[
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Blanchard took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7429. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            3714.5,
            0,
            1857.25,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1857.25
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 39 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 530 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            2340,
            1170,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1170
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson has Rs 4174 with him. He wants to buy avocado. One kg of avocado costs Rs 45. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of avocado?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley bought a phone which costed 6597 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 973 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            80,
            25,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 174, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "174",
            787,
            4,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 787
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "stem barks",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            4000,
            2000,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than pan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "flowers",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley bought a phone which costed 8851 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 606 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            50,
            2,
            11,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 275, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            32,
            "275",
            767,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 767
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "visiting cards",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 13 kg of meat in a day. Bradford 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 26 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 2 months ?",
        "options": [
            "468468468",
            "468",
            "468468",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "468"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Klein in Federated States Of Micronesia for 1 month = 9958. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            547,
            "9958",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 547
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 129?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Ritter in Wisconsin for 1 month = 17004. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            726,
            "17004",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 726
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Duarte bought a phone which costed 7449 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 630 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            24,
            0,
            52
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1046,
        "question": "Ron bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 5 meters, 30 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1046,
            2092,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 30 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            "270",
            1000,
            "270270270",
            "270270"
        ],
        "answer": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2000,
            1000,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": 790,
        "question": "Fleming bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 6 meters, 23 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            790,
            0,
            1580,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 46 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "4140",
            "41404140",
            "414041404140"
        ],
        "answer": "4140"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 153, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "153",
            869,
            "can be anything",
            33
        ],
        "answer": 869
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Gaines in Alabama for 1 month = 3023. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            934,
            "3023"
        ],
        "answer": 934
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 461 dollars of its actual cost which is 991 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 50 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            23050,
            46100
        ],
        "answer": 23050
    },
    {
        "answer": 894,
        "question": "Ashley bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 7 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1034.5,
            1788,
            894
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "sugar",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "crayons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 49 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 682 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 11 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            539,
            2,
            1078
        ],
        "answer": 539
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "2086 students from Idaho State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2790,
            4185,
            100,
            1395
        ],
        "answer": 1395
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 12 kg of meat in a day. Ron 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 311 physalis. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 86 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            4000,
            2000,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 816?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than pan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles has Rs 3071 with him. He wants to buy pamelo. One kg of pamelo costs Rs 36. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of pamelo?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Lawson 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9517 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 27 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 27*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Webster has Rs 3526 with him. He wants to buy lemon. One kg of lemon costs Rs 50. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of lemon?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 432 dollars of its actual cost which is 676 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 61 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            26352,
            52704,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 26352
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Mary in New York for 1 month = 6175. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            643,
            50000,
            "6175"
        ],
        "answer": 643
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bradford in Indiana for 1 month = 12047. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            96,
            50000,
            "12047"
        ],
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than jar. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1067,
        "question": "Jessie bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 13 meters, 27 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2134,
            0,
            1034.5,
            1067
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 301 gooseberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 60 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            15,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Krueger in Massachusetts for 1 month = 12488. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            749,
            50000,
            "12488"
        ],
        "answer": 749
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rich took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7402. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1233.6666666666667,
            0,
            30000,
            616.8333333333334
        ],
        "answer": 616.8333333333334
    },
    {
        "answer": 1363,
        "question": "Potts bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 7 meters, 33 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1363,
            2726,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce has Rs 517 with him. He wants to buy tangerine. One kg of tangerine costs Rs 27. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of tangerine?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "small diamonds",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            1000,
            2000
        ],
        "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "2887 students from Wyoming State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3744,
            1872,
            5616,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1872
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pepper",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 209 jambul. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 48 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "28011",
                "31621"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "28011",
            "31621"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 487 chicken. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 51 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            9,
            18,
            27,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 48 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 676 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 20 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1920,
            2,
            960,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 960
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruther bought a phone which costed 9587 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 736 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            17,
            2,
            60,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "3974 students from Guam State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            812,
            2436,
            100,
            1624
        ],
        "answer": 812
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than small tub. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "43315",
                "16317"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "43315",
            "16317"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "safety pins",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 297?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "8058",
                "51574"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "8058",
            "51574"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "hairbands",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "10635",
                "48997"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "10635",
            "48997"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 1429,
        "question": "Flynn bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 9 meters, 32 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1429,
            2858,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 23 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 678 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 21 tanks?",
        "options": [
            966,
            483,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 483
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1333,
        "question": "Bright bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 15 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            1333,
            0,
            2666
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 323, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            41,
            "can be anything",
            621,
            "323"
        ],
        "answer": 621
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Warner 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            12,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than kitchen dustbin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 217 dollars of its actual cost which is 683 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 50 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            10850,
            0,
            2,
            21700
        ],
        "answer": 10850
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 46 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 835 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1656,
            2,
            828
        ],
        "answer": 828
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 140 grapefruit. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 68 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "ATM cards",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Lloyd in Hawaii for 1 month = 4360. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            999,
            "4360"
        ],
        "answer": 999
    },
    {
        "question": "Schaefer bought a phone which costed 5532 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 591 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            48,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "1862 students from Illinois State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2691,
            1794,
            897,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 897
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 531?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 49 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 868 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 21 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            2058,
            1029,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1029
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than spoon. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "grass",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "44344",
                "15288"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "44344",
            "15288"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Freeman 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Hogan in Iowa for 1 month = 11139. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "11139",
            50000,
            951
        ],
        "answer": 951
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than kitchen dustbin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Bridges 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8921 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 19 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 19*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 926,
        "question": "Lloyd bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 9 meters, 22 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            926,
            0,
            1852
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Stein in Utah for 1 month = 18007. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            125,
            "18007"
        ],
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 472, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "472",
            10,
            "can be anything",
            660
        ],
        "answer": 660
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 821?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 833?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 321?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Ford in Michigan for 1 month = 13455. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "13455",
            50000,
            469
        ],
        "answer": 469
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Donovan 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            12,
            0,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mcgrath 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7873 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 27 hens of his village for which he will be paid 6 for each per day. Now he earns 27*6*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Freeman 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6481 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 22 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 22*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "Crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bradford has Rs 1746 with him. He wants to buy pomelo. One kg of pomelo costs Rs 49. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of pomelo?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Flynn in Virgin Islands for 1 month = 7976. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            987,
            "7976",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 987
    },
    {
        "question": "If 20 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 934 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 25 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            500,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 500
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice has Rs 3334 with him. He wants to buy kumquat. One kg of kumquat costs Rs 18. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of kumquat?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "chilli flakes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            800,
            0,
            400,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "400"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "14984",
                "44648"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "14984",
            "44648"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1000000,
            500,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "46949",
                "12683"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "46949",
            "12683"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 49 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 671 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 29 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1421,
            2,
            0,
            2842
        ],
        "answer": 1421
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 22 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "990",
            "990990",
            "990990990",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "990"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Crocodile",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8765. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1593.6363636363637,
            796.8181818181819,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 796.8181818181819
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Humpback whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "small diamonds",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1091,
        "question": "Stein bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 9 meters, 29 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2182,
            0,
            1091,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman bought a phone which costed 6447 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 925 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            76,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "paper clips",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles has Rs 3775 with him. He wants to buy bilberry. One kg of bilberry costs Rs 21. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of bilberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "4235 students from American Samoa State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4142,
            100,
            12426,
            8284
        ],
        "answer": 4142
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            2,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than juicer. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            16,
            0,
            1000000,
            32
        ],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "2530 students from Alaska State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1920,
            1280,
            640
        ],
        "answer": 640
    },
    {
        "question": "Esparza took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8220. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 7 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1174.2857142857142,
            2348.5714285714284,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1174.2857142857142
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "thermocol",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "58880",
                "752"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "58880",
            "752"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Clarke bought a phone which costed 7779 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 580 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            48
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Green anaconda",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson has Rs 1810 with him. He wants to buy bell pepper. One kg of bell pepper costs Rs 18. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of bell pepper?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "York has Rs 1174 with him. He wants to buy papaya. One kg of papaya costs Rs 45. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of papaya?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jessie bought a phone which costed 5776 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 713 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            23,
            2,
            58,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than kitchen dustbin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Clarke 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9702 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 28 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 28*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 137 kiwi fruit. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 97 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than glass. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "1603 students from Missouri State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            968,
            2904,
            1936,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 968
    },
    {
        "question": "If 42 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 940 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 21 tanks?",
        "options": [
            882,
            1764,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 882
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Humpback whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 49 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "3528",
            "352835283528",
            "35283528",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "3528"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Schaefer in New York for 1 month = 5098. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            624,
            50000,
            "5098"
        ],
        "answer": 624
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "4026 students from Nevada State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            3228,
            1076,
            2152
        ],
        "answer": 1076
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "hairbands",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Best 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6250 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 39 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 39*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tiffin box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 488, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            820,
            "488",
            21,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 820
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable glasses"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Jessie 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            22,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 454 cherry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 49 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            9,
            18,
            27,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Humpback whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            2500,
            0,
            5000,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "2500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 404 dollars of its actual cost which is 847 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 49 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            39592,
            2,
            19796,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 19796
    },
    {
        "question": "Bright bought a phone which costed 7425 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 685 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            16,
            2,
            56,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "474",
                "59158"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "474",
            "59158"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than juicer. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Ashley 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 316, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            747,
            40,
            "can be anything",
            "316"
        ],
        "answer": 747
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1250,
            1000000,
            2500,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "1250"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mccoy bought a phone which costed 9538 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 855 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            29,
            70,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 386 dollars of its actual cost which is 874 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 53 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            20458,
            40916,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 20458
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold",
            "disposable glasses"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "4679 students from Utah State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3706,
            11118,
            7412,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3706
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 13 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 817 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            156,
            312,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 458 rambutan. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 91 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            15,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "9951",
                "49681"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "9951",
            "49681"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 498 feijoa. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 39 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            36,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "If 32 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 837 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1152,
            576
        ],
        "answer": 576
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Gallegos 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8961 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 24 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 24*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley has Rs 3394 with him. He wants to buy jujube. One kg of jujube costs Rs 23. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of jujube?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Green anaconda",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "stem barks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 610?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "28013",
                "31619"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "28013",
            "31619"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Warner 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "stem barks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than coffee cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 456 dollars of its actual cost which is 758 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 37 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            16872,
            0,
            33744,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 16872
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "28282",
                "31350"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "28282",
            "31350"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "2006 students from Illinois State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            770,
            100,
            1540,
            2310
        ],
        "answer": 770
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 33?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 17 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "12241224",
            "1224",
            "122412241224",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1224"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "bobby pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 50 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 984 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1800,
            900,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 900
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glue sticks",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 136?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Charles in Minnesota for 1 month = 5983. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "5983",
            50000,
            920
        ],
        "answer": 920
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 262 dollars of its actual cost which is 994 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 23 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            12052,
            0,
            2,
            6026
        ],
        "answer": 6026
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            " Southern right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1053,
        "question": "Curry bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 16 meters, 11 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            2106,
            1053
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "tablets",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 207, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            894,
            48,
            "207",
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 894
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            100,
            1000000,
            200
        ],
        "answer": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Ruther 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson has Rs 1417 with him. He wants to buy plum. One kg of plum costs Rs 35. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of plum?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "crayons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "thermocol"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Harry 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6619 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 29*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Crosby 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            16,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "If 27 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 828 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 17 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            918,
            459
        ],
        "answer": 459
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Valentine bought a phone which costed 6686 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 766 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            0,
            62
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or cat ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 9 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "648648",
            "648648648",
            "648",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "648"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "58255",
                "1377"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "58255",
            "1377"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 48 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "2160",
            "21602160",
            1000,
            "216021602160"
        ],
        "answer": "2160"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "balloons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donaldson has Rs 2714 with him. He wants to buy pineapple. One kg of pineapple costs Rs 49. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of pineapple?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bruce in Maine for 1 month = 11403. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            744,
            "11403",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 744
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce bought a phone which costed 9402 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 798 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            66,
            2,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "Day has Rs 140 with him. He wants to buy grapefruit. One kg of grapefruit costs Rs 35. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of grapefruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "foam",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than jar. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "thermocol balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 110 pomelo. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 33 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 917?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 324 blood orange. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 33 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            9,
            18,
            27,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Fleming 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            7,
            0,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "31904",
                "27728"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "31904",
            "27728"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 523?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Mccoy in North Dakota for 1 month = 12354. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            248,
            50000,
            "12354"
        ],
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bright bought a phone which costed 5756 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 984 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            36,
            82,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Ruther 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "1874 students from Pennsylvania State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1709,
            5127,
            3418
        ],
        "answer": 1709
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stout took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7356. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1471.2,
            30000,
            2942.4
        ],
        "answer": 1471.2
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Day 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            10,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess bought a phone which costed 8696 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 821 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            68,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than glass. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "2984 students from New Jersey State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            2831,
            5662,
            8493
        ],
        "answer": 2831
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 27 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "17011701",
            1000,
            "1701",
            "170117011701"
        ],
        "answer": "1701"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails",
            "cookers"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 13 kg of meat in a day. Charles 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            12,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Sims 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            9,
            18,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "4500 students from New York State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5884,
            100,
            8826,
            2942
        ],
        "answer": 2942
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Hogan 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            11,
            0,
            40
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Jessie 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            20,
            5,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman bought a phone which costed 8509 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 994 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            82,
            14,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 23 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "14491449",
            "1449",
            "144914491449",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1449"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1734,
        "question": "Mcgrath bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 13 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            3468,
            0,
            1734
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "disposable glasses"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 49 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 682 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            588,
            1176
        ],
        "answer": 588
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mary 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8326 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 15 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 15*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donovan took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8488. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            2122.0,
            0,
            1061.0
        ],
        "answer": 1061.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 167 dollars of its actual cost which is 955 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 21 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3507,
            7014,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 3507
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "4416 students from Virginia State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1150,
            2300,
            3450
        ],
        "answer": 1150
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable plates",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Warren in Vermont for 1 month = 4824. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            777,
            "4824",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 777
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1297,
        "question": "Rice bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 6 meters, 30 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1297,
            2594
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 254?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallegos bought a phone which costed 8506 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 912 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            76,
            0,
            2,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Valenzuela 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6831 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 36 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 36*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "powder",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Gaines 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            14,
            0,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Freeman 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5363 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 35 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 35*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 886?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "43523",
                "16109"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "43523",
            "16109"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 24 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 6 months ?",
        "options": [
            "129612961296",
            1000,
            "12961296",
            "1296"
        ],
        "answer": "1296"
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts has Rs 3652 with him. He wants to buy bilberry. One kg of bilberry costs Rs 23. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of bilberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Warner in South Carolina for 1 month = 12951. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "12951",
            85
        ],
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "foam",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruther took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8414. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1682.8,
            3365.6,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1682.8
    },
    {
        "question": "4190 students from Oregon State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5823,
            100,
            1941,
            3882
        ],
        "answer": 1941
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "disposable glasses"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Ron 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "1706 students from Delaware State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4323,
            1441,
            100,
            2882
        ],
        "answer": 1441
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley bought a phone which costed 6023 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 903 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            74,
            2,
            0,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            100,
            200
        ],
        "answer": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd bought a phone which costed 5484 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 661 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            6,
            54,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable glasses",
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bradford took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9487. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            1581.1666666666667,
            790.5833333333334
        ],
        "answer": 790.5833333333334
    },
    {
        "answer": 1590,
        "question": "Rice bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 5 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3180,
            1034.5,
            1590
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8869. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            739.0833333333334,
            1478.1666666666667,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 739.0833333333334
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess has Rs 207 with him. He wants to buy ugli fruit. One kg of ugli fruit costs Rs 36. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of ugli fruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 717?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1690,
        "question": "Warner bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 5 meters, 39 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1690,
            3380,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 120 dollars of its actual cost which is 605 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 55 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            6600,
            13200
        ],
        "answer": 6600
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "4845 students from North Carolina State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3680,
            7360,
            100,
            11040
        ],
        "answer": 3680
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 413, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "413",
            48,
            "can be anything",
            960
        ],
        "answer": 960
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 42 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "18901890",
            "1890",
            1000,
            "189018901890"
        ],
        "answer": "1890"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 1?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mccoy has Rs 776 with him. He wants to buy purple mangosteen. One kg of purple mangosteen costs Rs 24. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of purple mangosteen?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            800,
            400
        ],
        "answer": "400"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Donaldson 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6953 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 13 hens of his village for which he will be paid 6 for each per day. Now he earns 13*6*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Hess 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "2845 students from Hawaii State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5228,
            7842,
            2614,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2614
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 150, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            49,
            "can be anything",
            "150",
            868
        ],
        "answer": 868
    },
    {
        "question": "If 28 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 544 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 11 tanks?",
        "options": [
            308,
            2,
            616,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            1000,
            2000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Booker bought a phone which costed 5949 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 830 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            28,
            68,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "3419 students from Puerto Rico State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1328,
            3984,
            2656
        ],
        "answer": 1328
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 671?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Miller in Arizona for 1 month = 6235. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "6235",
            816
        ],
        "answer": 816
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 37 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 672 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 26 tanks?",
        "options": [
            962,
            2,
            1924,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 962
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            25,
            0,
            50,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "chilli flakes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 289 fish. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 70 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermocol balls",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Donaldson 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            12,
            0,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable plates",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 185 canary melon. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 76 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 321 persimmon. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 80 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "57670",
                "1962"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "57670",
            "1962"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgan bought a phone which costed 5888 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 626 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            21,
            2,
            52
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Valenzuela 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9874 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 35 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 35*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 401 dollars of its actual cost which is 816 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 64 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            51328,
            2,
            25664,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 25664
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Li bought a phone which costed 9541 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 936 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            39,
            0,
            2,
            78
        ],
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley has Rs 4391 with him. He wants to buy tomato. One kg of tomato costs Rs 18. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of tomato?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "14513",
                "45119"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "14513",
            "45119"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable plates",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Cox in Marshall Islands for 1 month = 8527. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "8527",
            50000,
            28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mccoy has Rs 837 with him. He wants to buy redcurrant. One kg of redcurrant costs Rs 48. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of redcurrant?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9415. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            784.5833333333334,
            30000,
            1569.1666666666667,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 784.5833333333334
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hogan took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9923. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2480.75,
            4961.5,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2480.75
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            800,
            400,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "400"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            10000,
            0,
            1000000,
            5000
        ],
        "answer": "5000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Valentine has Rs 4401 with him. He wants to buy nut. One kg of nut costs Rs 19. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of nut?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tablets",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "puffed rice",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "answer": 937,
        "question": "Conway bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 6 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            937,
            1874
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Bright 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "4260 students from Tennessee State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            7587,
            2529,
            5058
        ],
        "answer": 2529
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 365, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            12,
            "can be anything",
            539,
            "365"
        ],
        "answer": 539
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 447?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than saucepan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Rice in Pennsylvania for 1 month = 12508. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            585,
            "12508"
        ],
        "answer": 585
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Gaines in Nevada for 1 month = 1547. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "1547",
            50000,
            136
        ],
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "2510 students from Iowa State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4473,
            1491,
            100,
            2982
        ],
        "answer": 1491
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "1288 students from Puerto Rico State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3138,
            2092,
            1046,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1046
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Donaldson 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6668 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 14 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 14*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Stout in Idaho for 1 month = 14581. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            324,
            50000,
            "14581"
        ],
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "Stein took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7250. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            805.5555555555555,
            0,
            1611.111111111111
        ],
        "answer": 805.5555555555555
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Stein in Kentucky for 1 month = 8603. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            226,
            "8603",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 38 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            "13681368",
            "1368",
            "136813681368",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1368"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts has Rs 1266 with him. He wants to buy raspberry. One kg of raspberry costs Rs 22. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of raspberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "bobby pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "4460 students from Alaska State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            8811,
            5874,
            2937,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2937
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "foam",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "feather",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than glass. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 59, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            747,
            50,
            "59",
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 747
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Schaefer bought a phone which costed 8195 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 753 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            25,
            2,
            0,
            62
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 354 dollars of its actual cost which is 906 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 39 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            13806,
            27612
        ],
        "answer": 13806
    },
    {
        "question": "Bridges has Rs 3410 with him. He wants to buy eggplant. One kg of eggplant costs Rs 25. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of eggplant?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 975?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Li 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7725 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 10 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 10*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "56944",
                "2688"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "56944",
            "2688"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 49 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "529252925292",
            "52925292",
            "5292"
        ],
        "answer": "5292"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 278 blood orange. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 40 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            400,
            200,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "paper clips",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "1743 students from Missouri State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            820,
            100,
            1230,
            410
        ],
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7340. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1468.0,
            0,
            2936.0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1468.0
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 42 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 992 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            966,
            1932
        ],
        "answer": 966
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Rich 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7682 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 19 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 19*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 99, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            40,
            "99",
            673,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 673
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Morgan 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 37 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "23312331",
            "2331",
            "233123312331",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "2331"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Mary 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6974 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 33 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 33*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 29 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 773 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 20 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1160,
            0,
            580,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 580
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Sims 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            36,
            7,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "answer": 970,
        "question": "Ashley bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 13 meters, 24 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1940,
            970,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "1023",
                "58609"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "1023",
            "58609"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 310 physalis. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 42 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Crocodile",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            50,
            25,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "pearls",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bobby pins",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 835?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Mike 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            8,
            3,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable glasses",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "nails",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "34317",
                "25315"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "34317",
            "25315"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Booker bought a phone which costed 9698 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 740 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            11,
            60
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "2791 students from California State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            2456,
            3684,
            1228
        ],
        "answer": 1228
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "2840 students from West Virginia State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3144,
            1572,
            100,
            4716
        ],
        "answer": 1572
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Ritter in Wisconsin for 1 month = 15463. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            276,
            "15463",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            5000,
            0,
            2500,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "2500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "4429",
                "55203"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "4429",
            "55203"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 250 cloudberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 78 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 36 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 2 months ?",
        "options": [
            "648648",
            "648648648",
            1000,
            "648"
        ],
        "answer": "648"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5338. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2669.0,
            30000,
            0,
            1334.5
        ],
        "answer": 1334.5
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Li 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            10,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "visiting cards"
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "small diamonds",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Cox 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8453 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 40 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 40*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "3555 students from Virgin Islands State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3076,
            6152,
            9228,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3076
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            " Southern right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Miller in Louisiana for 1 month = 12237. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "12237",
            912
        ],
        "answer": 912
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Cox 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            8,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1568,
        "question": "Warner bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 12 meters, 32 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1568,
            3136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "1443",
                "58189"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "1443",
            "58189"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Crosby 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7079 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 27 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 27*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1521,
        "question": "Hogan bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 14 meters, 35 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3042,
            1521,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Clarke bought a phone which costed 6632 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 530 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            0,
            44
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": 915,
        "question": "Clarke bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 5 meters, 23 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            915,
            1034.5,
            0,
            1830
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kim bought a phone which costed 9579 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 785 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            64,
            23,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 265 dollars of its actual cost which is 922 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 39 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            20670,
            10335
        ],
        "answer": 10335
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 20 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 752 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 26 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            520,
            1040
        ],
        "answer": 520
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Humpback whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 249 dollars of its actual cost which is 766 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 42 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            20916,
            10458
        ],
        "answer": 10458
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 192, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            574,
            14,
            "192",
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 574
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 204, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            887,
            "can be anything",
            42,
            "204"
        ],
        "answer": 887
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Curry bought a phone which costed 7511 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 816 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            68,
            0,
            2,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 12 kg of meat in a day. Valentine 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Ruther in West Virginia for 1 month = 18562. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "18562",
            50000,
            636
        ],
        "answer": 636
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "gift wraps",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            500,
            0,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "500"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than juicer. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Sims 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            8,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "1735 students from Washington State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1449,
            4347,
            100,
            2898
        ],
        "answer": 1449
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Rich 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mary 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6211 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 15 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 15*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 499?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Day 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5796 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 18 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 18*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "ATM cards",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 308?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "58978",
                "654"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "58978",
            "654"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1410,
        "question": "Donaldson bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 13 meters, 29 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2820,
            1410,
            0,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford has Rs 2319 with him. He wants to buy cucumber. One kg of cucumber costs Rs 39. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of cucumber?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 46 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 837 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            1104,
            0,
            552
        ],
        "answer": 552
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "candies",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Harry 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9041 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 22 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 22*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Chervy 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7219 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 34 hens of his village for which he will be paid 6 for each per day. Now he earns 34*6*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "pearls",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Charles 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            20,
            1000000,
            0,
            10
        ],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Conway in Virginia for 1 month = 1395. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "1395",
            20,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Cox 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 266 redcurrant. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 93 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "58291",
                "1341"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "58291",
            "1341"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": 921,
        "question": "Donovan bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 14 meters, 7 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            921,
            1842,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "17983",
                "41649"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "17983",
            "41649"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 1624,
        "question": "Booker bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 12 meters, 34 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1624,
            3248,
            0,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tom took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8813. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            1101.625,
            0,
            2203.25
        ],
        "answer": 1101.625
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 451?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "wall pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 40 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 880 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            480,
            0,
            2,
            960
        ],
        "answer": 480
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley has Rs 1379 with him. He wants to buy strawberry. One kg of strawberry costs Rs 20. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of strawberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 179 durian. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 88 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Kim in South Dakota for 1 month = 12442. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            104,
            "12442"
        ],
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than measuring cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kim has Rs 4074 with him. He wants to buy rock melon. One kg of rock melon costs Rs 49. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of rock melon?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 493 dollars of its actual cost which is 760 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 60 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            59160,
            2,
            0,
            29580
        ],
        "answer": 29580
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "shells",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 14 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 903 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 14 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            392,
            196,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            5000,
            10000
        ],
        "answer": "5000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Buckley in Washington for 1 month = 18435. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "18435",
            59,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "candies"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 301 eggplant. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 68 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "crayons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "answer": 789,
        "question": "Tom bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 10 meters, 20 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1578,
            1034.5,
            789
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 200, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            705,
            40,
            "200"
        ],
        "answer": 705
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Lloyd in Alabama for 1 month = 17914. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "17914",
            50000,
            518
        ],
        "answer": 518
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "safety pins",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "York 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8208 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 34 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 34*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mary 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7933 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 16 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 16*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Serrano bought a phone which costed 8775 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 976 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            80,
            8,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 253 dollars of its actual cost which is 632 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 38 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            19228,
            9614,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 9614
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 19 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "136813681368",
            "1368",
            1000,
            "13681368"
        ],
        "answer": "1368"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 18 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "162",
            "162162162",
            "162162"
        ],
        "answer": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gilbert took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7592. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            843.5555555555555,
            0,
            30000,
            1687.111111111111
        ],
        "answer": 843.5555555555555
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 161?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Crosby in California for 1 month = 9748. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            106,
            "9748"
        ],
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 978?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 34 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 932 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            782,
            1564,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 782
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stout took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8380. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            3352.0,
            1676.0
        ],
        "answer": 1676.0
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Blanchard 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9177 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 37 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 37*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 187 apple. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 94 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 31 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 604 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            713,
            2,
            0,
            1426
        ],
        "answer": 713
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 431 breadfruit. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 49 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            8,
            16,
            24,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 329 dollars of its actual cost which is 660 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 62 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            20398,
            0,
            40796,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 20398
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 117, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "117",
            "can be anything",
            652,
            46
        ],
        "answer": 652
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Hebert in Minnesota for 1 month = 9272. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "9272",
            31
        ],
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "30786",
                "28846"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "30786",
            "28846"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 16 kg of meat in a day. Miller 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            8,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than saucepan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 10 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 553 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 20 tanks?",
        "options": [
            200,
            0,
            2,
            400
        ],
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 322 jambul. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 35 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            9,
            18,
            27,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 796?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "feather",
            "cookers"
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Stein 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8414 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 14 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 14*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conway took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9693. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            881.1818181818181,
            1762.3636363636363,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 881.1818181818181
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 81, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            12,
            "can be anything",
            508,
            "81"
        ],
        "answer": 508
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 23 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 509 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 25 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1150,
            2,
            575,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 575
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hogan took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5438. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 2 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            5438.0,
            2719.0,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2719.0
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "55889",
                "3743"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "55889",
            "3743"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Miller 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            20,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "2239 students from Texas State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1885,
            5655,
            3770,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1885
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "ATM cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glue sticks",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "3890 students from Wyoming State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            795,
            2385,
            1590
        ],
        "answer": 795
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Oconnor 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8510 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 29*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruther took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6192. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1548.0,
            30000,
            3096.0,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1548.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1539,
        "question": "Meadows bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 15 meters, 33 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3078,
            1034.5,
            0,
            1539
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 7 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "315315",
            "315315315",
            "315",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "315"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "stem barks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Krueger took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8268. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1033.5,
            30000,
            2067.0
        ],
        "answer": 1033.5
    },
    {
        "answer": 1780,
        "question": "Duarte bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 6 meters, 40 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3560,
            1780,
            0,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 237, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            7,
            "can be anything",
            "237",
            799
        ],
        "answer": 799
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "51639",
                "7993"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "51639",
            "7993"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "paper clips",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 43 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 569 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 16 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1376,
            0,
            2,
            688
        ],
        "answer": 688
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Warner 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9971 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 29*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 251, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            "251",
            21,
            889
        ],
        "answer": 889
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 800?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than blender. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 153, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            31,
            898,
            "153"
        ],
        "answer": 898
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7563. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            687.5454545454545,
            1375.090909090909,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 687.5454545454545
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 211, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            48,
            752,
            "211",
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 752
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "1729 students from North Dakota State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            3216,
            2144,
            1072
        ],
        "answer": 1072
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 147 dollars of its actual cost which is 716 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 22 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            3234,
            2,
            0,
            6468
        ],
        "answer": 3234
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 38 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "273627362736",
            1000,
            "27362736",
            "2736"
        ],
        "answer": "2736"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 11 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1089",
            "108910891089",
            1000,
            "10891089"
        ],
        "answer": "1089"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pencils",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice bought a phone which costed 9555 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 512 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            42,
            2,
            15,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            250,
            0,
            1000000,
            500
        ],
        "answer": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "chilli flakes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 50 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "315031503150",
            1000,
            "31503150",
            "3150"
        ],
        "answer": "3150"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 12 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 807 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 27 tanks?",
        "options": [
            648,
            324,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 60, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            952,
            "can be anything",
            "60",
            22
        ],
        "answer": 952
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 193 pear. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 97 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "visiting cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Lawson 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7271 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 13 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 13*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Harry 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9135 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 19 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 19*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Clarke in New Jersey for 1 month = 3670. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            596,
            50000,
            "3670"
        ],
        "answer": 596
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Sims 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8140 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 20 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 20*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 19 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 888 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 20 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            760,
            0,
            380
        ],
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Hess 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            28,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Green anaconda",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bright bought a phone which costed 6928 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 785 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            20,
            64
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 522?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Crocodile",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 179, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "179",
            645,
            20,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 645
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            2000,
            4000
        ],
        "answer": "2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 236 dollars of its actual cost which is 921 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 57 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            13452,
            26904,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 13452
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 138, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            5,
            "can be anything",
            555,
            "138"
        ],
        "answer": 555
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 10 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            "270270",
            1000,
            "270270270",
            "270"
        ],
        "answer": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            10,
            20
        ],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 16 kg of meat in a day. Mary 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            32,
            0,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Ritter in Minnesota for 1 month = 7005. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "7005",
            502
        ],
        "answer": 502
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mccoy 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9646 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 36 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 36*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "wall pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 437 dollars of its actual cost which is 698 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 51 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            44574,
            22287,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 22287
    },
    {
        "question": "4811 students from New Jersey State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            6398,
            100,
            9597,
            3199
        ],
        "answer": 3199
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 24 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1080",
            1000,
            "108010801080",
            "10801080"
        ],
        "answer": "1080"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "chilli flakes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 410 boysenberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 40 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            10,
            20,
            30,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 209 dollars of its actual cost which is 993 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 56 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            11704,
            23408
        ],
        "answer": 11704
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley has Rs 2373 with him. He wants to buy chili pepper. One kg of chili pepper costs Rs 38. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of chili pepper?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Henry in Wisconsin for 1 month = 2233. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "2233",
            114
        ],
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 197 dollars of its actual cost which is 730 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 23 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4531,
            0,
            9062
        ],
        "answer": 4531
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 92?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "candies"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Donovan 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8824 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 15 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 15*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bright has Rs 208 with him. He wants to buy fig. One kg of fig costs Rs 28. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of fig?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pearls",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "15722",
                "43910"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "15722",
            "43910"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mccoy bought a phone which costed 8537 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 537 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            8,
            44
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "answer": 1028,
        "question": "Mike bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 10 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2056,
            0,
            1028,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 500 dollars of its actual cost which is 883 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 68 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            68000,
            34000,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 34000
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley bought a phone which costed 9491 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 691 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            56,
            2,
            0,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 256, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            694,
            44,
            "256"
        ],
        "answer": 694
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "shells",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 47 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 615 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 13 tanks?",
        "options": [
            611,
            1222,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 611
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 165 dollars of its actual cost which is 981 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 65 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            10725,
            2,
            21450,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 10725
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Lloyd in Nevada for 1 month = 17030. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            44,
            "17030",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 169, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            "169",
            503,
            45
        ],
        "answer": 503
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "27923",
                "31709"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "27923",
            "31709"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            200,
            1000000,
            400
        ],
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 989?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 26 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 680 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            312,
            624
        ],
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "1154 students from Mississippi State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2218,
            1109,
            3327,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1109
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 12 kg of meat in a day. Krueger 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 170, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            803,
            "170",
            11,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 803
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            20,
            10
        ],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Sims 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 406, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            908,
            "can be anything",
            "406",
            47
        ],
        "answer": 908
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 33 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            "891",
            1000,
            "891891891",
            "891891"
        ],
        "answer": "891"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 18 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 811 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 28 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1008,
            2,
            504,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 504
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "29893",
                "29739"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "29893",
            "29739"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 235 cloudberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 75 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 36 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "25922592",
            "259225922592",
            "2592",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "2592"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Rice 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 208 dollars of its actual cost which is 852 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 32 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            13312,
            2,
            0,
            6656
        ],
        "answer": 6656
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 157 goji berry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 57 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Valentine bought a phone which costed 7955 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 982 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            80,
            0,
            2,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bright has Rs 769 with him. He wants to buy satsuma. One kg of satsuma costs Rs 16. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of satsuma?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "lollipops",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Morgan in Arizona for 1 month = 16666. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            941,
            "16666"
        ],
        "answer": 941
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crosby took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9840. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            1968.0,
            984.0
        ],
        "answer": 984.0
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 219 pamelo. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 81 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5422. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1084.4,
            2168.8,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1084.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Ford 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 162, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            9,
            738,
            "162"
        ],
        "answer": 738
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 550?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Blanchard took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8773. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1595.090909090909,
            30000,
            0,
            797.5454545454545
        ],
        "answer": 797.5454545454545
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 12 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 597 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            360,
            2,
            0,
            720
        ],
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            625,
            0,
            1000000,
            1250
        ],
        "answer": "625"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 993?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Hebert in Maine for 1 month = 2721. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "2721",
            666
        ],
        "answer": 666
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            5000,
            1000000,
            2500
        ],
        "answer": "2500"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "York has Rs 4123 with him. He wants to buy avocado. One kg of avocado costs Rs 26. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of avocado?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ron has Rs 410 with him. He wants to buy gooseberry. One kg of gooseberry costs Rs 22. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of gooseberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "candies"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hebert has Rs 4752 with him. He wants to buy blackberry. One kg of blackberry costs Rs 20. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of blackberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 479 purple mangosteen. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 82 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            15,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1000000,
            0,
            4
        ],
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donovan took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6432. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            643.2,
            1286.4,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 643.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 198 dollars of its actual cost which is 813 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 62 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            24552,
            12276,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 12276
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermocol balls",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Conley 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "3380 students from Palau State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            7191,
            4794,
            100,
            2397
        ],
        "answer": 2397
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stout has Rs 3905 with him. He wants to buy apricot. One kg of apricot costs Rs 16. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of apricot?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "answer": 930,
        "question": "Henry bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 5 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            930,
            1860,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 243 dollars of its actual cost which is 720 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 52 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            25272,
            2,
            12636,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 12636
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "46057",
                "13575"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "46057",
            "13575"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 479, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            37,
            "can be anything",
            597,
            "479"
        ],
        "answer": 597
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 267 tamarillo. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 59 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "42423",
                "17209"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "42423",
            "17209"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "answer": 2000,
        "question": "Warren bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 16 meters, 12 meters, 40 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            4000,
            2000,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "36964",
                "22668"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "36964",
            "22668"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "hairbands",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 17 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            "612612",
            "612",
            1000,
            "612612612"
        ],
        "answer": "612"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Conway in Federated States Of Micronesia for 1 month = 19835. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            266,
            50000,
            "19835"
        ],
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 46 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "1656",
            "16561656",
            "165616561656"
        ],
        "answer": "1656"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            1250,
            625
        ],
        "answer": "625"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "3926 students from Arizona State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3264,
            4896,
            1632,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1632
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 26 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 819 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 29 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            754,
            1508,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 754
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": 964,
        "question": "Bruce bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 12 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1928,
            0,
            1034.5,
            964
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "pearls"
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "3401 students from Washington State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3609,
            100,
            1203,
            2406
        ],
        "answer": 1203
    },
    {
        "answer": 1565,
        "question": "Cox bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 13 meters, 36 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3130,
            1034.5,
            0,
            1565
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Mcgrath 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            12,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shells",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1713,
        "question": "Mcgrath bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 13 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3426,
            0,
            1713,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than jar. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "lollipops",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath bought a phone which costed 8527 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 939 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            11,
            78
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley has Rs 2120 with him. He wants to buy dragonfruit. One kg of dragonfruit costs Rs 30. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of dragonfruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "pepper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 32 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 740 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1472,
            736,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 736
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chervy bought a phone which costed 7431 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 698 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            58,
            14,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 235, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            702,
            "can be anything",
            19,
            "235"
        ],
        "answer": 702
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 17 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1683",
            "168316831683",
            1000,
            "16831683"
        ],
        "answer": "1683"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "foam",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "safety pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 289 raspberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 48 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "grass",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            8,
            4,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Rice 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            18,
            0,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Li has Rs 4493 with him. He wants to buy avocado. One kg of avocado costs Rs 42. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of avocado?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            18,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Valenzuela 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9807 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 28 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 28*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 190, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "190",
            11,
            "can be anything",
            727
        ],
        "answer": 727
    },
    {
        "answer": 1179,
        "question": "Morgan bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 15 meters, 27 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1179,
            0,
            2358,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            40,
            0,
            80,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 232?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "paper clips",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            800,
            1000000,
            400,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "400"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 106 lime. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 96 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 473, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            869,
            "473",
            27,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 869
    },
    {
        "answer": 1637,
        "question": "Schaefer bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 7 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            1637,
            0,
            3274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ron took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7159. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 1 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            7159.0,
            30000,
            14318.0
        ],
        "answer": 7159.0
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Curry 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8202 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 13 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 13*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 43 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 672 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            2580,
            0,
            1290
        ],
        "answer": 1290
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 131 dollars of its actual cost which is 722 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 52 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            6812,
            2,
            0,
            13624
        ],
        "answer": 6812
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Donovan in Puerto Rico for 1 month = 7884. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "7884",
            50000,
            343
        ],
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            8,
            16
        ],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8885. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1777.0,
            3554.0,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1777.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Blanchard took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9390. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            2347.5,
            1173.75,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1173.75
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "safety pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleming bought a phone which costed 5913 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 842 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            12,
            0,
            70
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Bridges 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7516 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 24 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 24*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Blanchard took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8384. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            698.6666666666666,
            1397.3333333333333,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 698.6666666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            20000,
            10000,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "10000"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 37 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 549 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 14 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            1036,
            518,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 518
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "flowers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 165 currant. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 79 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "52099",
                "7533"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "52099",
            "7533"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Conway 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8757 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 18 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 18*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 342?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "3928 students from Rhode Island State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1602,
            801,
            2403,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 801
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donaldson bought a phone which costed 6953 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 886 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            15,
            72,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 385?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "visiting card"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 153 dollars of its actual cost which is 855 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 50 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            7650,
            0,
            15300
        ],
        "answer": 7650
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "35173",
                "24459"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "35173",
            "24459"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 315 cloudberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 79 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 489 dollars of its actual cost which is 703 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 69 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            67482,
            2,
            0,
            33741
        ],
        "answer": 33741
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "10634",
                "48998"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "10634",
            "48998"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bobby pins",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 472 banana. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 100 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 627?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 1213,
        "question": "Kim bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 13 meters, 30 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1213,
            1034.5,
            2426
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Day 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6729 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 20 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 20*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 252, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            17,
            "252",
            "can be anything",
            862
        ],
        "answer": 862
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 494 passionfruit. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 80 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "keys",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 266 pear. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 69 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops",
            "cookers"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "45981",
                "13651"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "45981",
            "13651"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "4154 students from Rhode Island State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5066,
            100,
            7599,
            2533
        ],
        "answer": 2533
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 155?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "crayons",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Moyer 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            36,
            15,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "58978",
                "654"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "58978",
            "654"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "22909",
                "36723"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "22909",
            "36723"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "grass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Hess 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7235 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 38 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 38*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ritter has Rs 4394 with him. He wants to buy honeydew. One kg of honeydew costs Rs 37. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of honeydew?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Potts in Connecticut for 1 month = 1710. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "1710",
            438
        ],
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 156, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            652,
            8,
            "can be anything",
            "156"
        ],
        "answer": 652
    },
    {
        "question": "1639 students from Connecticut State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            953,
            2859,
            100,
            1906
        ],
        "answer": 953
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable glasses",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "foam",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than juicer. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Gaines 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crosby has Rs 2049 with him. He wants to buy bilberry. One kg of bilberry costs Rs 34. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of bilberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than plate. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 856?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 168, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            939,
            "168",
            42,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 939
    },
    {
        "question": "Bridges bought a phone which costed 5903 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 806 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            21,
            2,
            66,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Lloyd 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6188 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 21 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 21*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Li 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donaldson took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8633. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 3 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2877.6666666666665,
            5755.333333333333,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2877.6666666666665
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallegos took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5845. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2338.0,
            30000,
            1169.0,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1169.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 279 dollars of its actual cost which is 609 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 54 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            15066,
            30132
        ],
        "answer": 15066
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than tin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            8,
            0,
            16
        ],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 374 pomegranate. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 51 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Bridges 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tablets",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 336 dollars of its actual cost which is 752 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 29 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            9744,
            2,
            19488
        ],
        "answer": 9744
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            4000,
            0,
            1000000,
            2000
        ],
        "answer": "2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 5 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            "4545",
            "454545",
            "45",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than coffee cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1540,
        "question": "Curry bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 10 meters, 36 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1540,
            1034.5,
            0,
            3080
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "visiting cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Kim 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            7,
            16,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "bobby pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 45 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 802 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1035,
            2070,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 1035
    },
    {
        "question": "1748 students from California State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1366,
            2049,
            683,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 683
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "flowers",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Flynn bought a phone which costed 9974 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 607 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            50,
            24,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 20 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "1440",
            "144014401440",
            "14401440"
        ],
        "answer": "1440"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conway took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8647. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1080.875,
            0,
            2161.75,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1080.875
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "chilli flakes",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 38 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1710",
            "17101710",
            1000,
            "171017101710"
        ],
        "answer": "1710"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 18 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 529 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 11 tanks?",
        "options": [
            198,
            396,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Valenzuela 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7392 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 11 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 11*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 993?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9019. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            3607.6,
            0,
            1803.8
        ],
        "answer": 1803.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice has Rs 2533 with him. He wants to buy tomato. One kg of tomato costs Rs 45. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of tomato?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 50 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 792 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 25 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1250,
            2,
            0,
            2500
        ],
        "answer": 1250
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley bought a phone which costed 6844 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 830 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            68,
            2,
            0,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 495, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            43,
            946,
            "can be anything",
            "495"
        ],
        "answer": 946
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 286 olive. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 54 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            15,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than small tub. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "2628 students from West Virginia State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1683,
            5049,
            3366
        ],
        "answer": 1683
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "10837",
                "48795"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "10837",
            "48795"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 493, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            11,
            "493",
            814,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 814
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 28 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 9 months ?",
        "options": [
            "226822682268",
            1000,
            "2268",
            "22682268"
        ],
        "answer": "2268"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "salt",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 476 dollars of its actual cost which is 685 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 55 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            26180,
            52360,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 26180
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "socks",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tumbler. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than kitchen dustbin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable glasses",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "1529 students from Maine State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2883,
            100,
            961,
            1922
        ],
        "answer": 961
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "1877 students from Tennessee State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3939,
            2626,
            100,
            1313
        ],
        "answer": 1313
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Booker took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6092. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 6 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            2030.6666666666667,
            1015.3333333333334
        ],
        "answer": 1015.3333333333334
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Esparza 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            3,
            30,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than jar. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 197?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than tiffin box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 6 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            "540540540",
            "540",
            1000,
            "540540"
        ],
        "answer": "540"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 34 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 884 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 10 tanks?",
        "options": [
            680,
            0,
            340,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 257, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            28,
            532,
            "can be anything",
            "257"
        ],
        "answer": 532
    },
    {
        "question": "If 28 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 883 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 13 tanks?",
        "options": [
            364,
            2,
            0,
            728
        ],
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "2617 students from Oklahoma State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5649,
            100,
            3766,
            1883
        ],
        "answer": 1883
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Miller took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6492. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1623.0,
            0,
            30000,
            3246.0
        ],
        "answer": 1623.0
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "thermocol",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "3317 students from North Carolina State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            6182,
            100,
            9273,
            3091
        ],
        "answer": 3091
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "13622",
                "46010"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "13622",
            "46010"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Jessie in Indiana for 1 month = 3788. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            702,
            50000,
            "3788"
        ],
        "answer": 702
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 990?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than tea kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford has Rs 3983 with him. He wants to buy kiwi fruit. One kg of kiwi fruit costs Rs 32. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of kiwi fruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Buckley 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6332 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 10 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 10*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 17 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            "183618361836",
            "1836",
            "18361836",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1836"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 13?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 13?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Warner in Indiana for 1 month = 2195. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "2195",
            962,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 962
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Valenzuela took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5743. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            478.5833333333333,
            30000,
            0,
            957.1666666666666
        ],
        "answer": 478.5833333333333
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1481,
        "question": "Moyer bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 15 meters, 34 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1481,
            2962
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "1875 students from Texas State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4701,
            100,
            3134,
            1567
        ],
        "answer": 1567
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 262 dollars of its actual cost which is 975 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 24 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            12576,
            6288,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 6288
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 19 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 9 months ?",
        "options": [
            "153915391539",
            "15391539",
            "1539",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1539"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "3328 students from North Carolina State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            6260,
            9390,
            3130
        ],
        "answer": 3130
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 107 dollars of its actual cost which is 978 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 34 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            3638,
            7276,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 3638
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 27 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            "2916",
            1000,
            "291629162916",
            "29162916"
        ],
        "answer": "2916"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 11 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 944 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 28 tanks?",
        "options": [
            616,
            2,
            0,
            308
        ],
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "Fin whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than bottle cap. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 454 dollars of its actual cost which is 795 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 64 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            58112,
            29056,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 29056
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 369 dollars of its actual cost which is 740 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 34 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            12546,
            25092
        ],
        "answer": 12546
    },
    {
        "question": "1186 students from New Jersey State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            980,
            1470,
            490,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 490
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 407?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than jar. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 857?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "foam",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 22 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "2178",
            "21782178",
            "217821782178"
        ],
        "answer": "2178"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 13 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 922 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            390,
            780
        ],
        "answer": 390
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd has Rs 4109 with him. He wants to buy apricot. One kg of apricot costs Rs 23. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of apricot?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "31302",
                "28330"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "31302",
            "28330"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr has Rs 574 with him. He wants to buy durian. One kg of durian costs Rs 27. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of durian?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Harry 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 30 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 968 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1080,
            2,
            540,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 540
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Best has Rs 1532 with him. He wants to buy damson. One kg of damson costs Rs 50. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of damson?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 45 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 662 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 27 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1215,
            2430
        ],
        "answer": 1215
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "tree leaves",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Esparza has Rs 2373 with him. He wants to buy currant. One kg of currant costs Rs 46. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of currant?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 19 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 761 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 27 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            513,
            0,
            1026
        ],
        "answer": 513
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 390, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            42,
            "390",
            671
        ],
        "answer": 671
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "24527",
                "35105"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "24527",
            "35105"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "9113",
                "50519"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "9113",
            "50519"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "thermocol"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 21 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "189189189",
            "189",
            "189189"
        ],
        "answer": "189"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Oconnor 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7040 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 39 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 39*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Crocodile",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Ruther 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "If 48 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 665 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 22 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2112,
            1056,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1056
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgan took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8283. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 2 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            8283.0,
            4141.5
        ],
        "answer": 4141.5
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 470 tamarillo. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 35 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            13,
            26,
            39,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Brooks in Florida for 1 month = 6247. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "6247",
            849
        ],
        "answer": 849
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "Green anaconda",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 403 raspberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 58 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 17 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "12241224",
            "122412241224",
            "1224",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1224"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman bought a phone which costed 7799 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 773 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            64,
            27,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shells",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chervy has Rs 3111 with him. He wants to buy pear. One kg of pear costs Rs 17. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of pear?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "small diamonds",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 784?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Booker took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6650. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 3 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2216.6666666666665,
            0,
            30000,
            4433.333333333333
        ],
        "answer": 2216.6666666666665
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 107 dollars of its actual cost which is 767 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 24 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            2568,
            0,
            5136
        ],
        "answer": 2568
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 44 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 680 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2640,
            1320,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1320
    },
    {
        "answer": 1427,
        "question": "Conley bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 9 meters, 35 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2854,
            1427,
            0,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Buckley in South Carolina for 1 month = 11670. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "11670",
            831,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 831
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Donaldson 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            20,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "answer": 779,
        "question": "Oconnor bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 9 meters, 23 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            779,
            1034.5,
            1558
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than spoon. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 29 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 660 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 27 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1566,
            2,
            783
        ],
        "answer": 783
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than tumbler. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 662?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 11 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            "990",
            "990990990",
            "990990",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "990"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Henry 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8125 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 23 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 23*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Flynn 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            5,
            36,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Esparza in Massachusetts for 1 month = 1732. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            449,
            "1732",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 449
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Serrano 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Best has Rs 3877 with him. He wants to buy gooseberry. One kg of gooseberry costs Rs 47. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of gooseberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 146, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            925,
            "can be anything",
            "146",
            12
        ],
        "answer": 925
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "1038 students from Nevada State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            2265,
            1510,
            755
        ],
        "answer": 755
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks has Rs 261 with him. He wants to buy rambutan. One kg of rambutan costs Rs 35. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of rambutan?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 32 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            "345634563456",
            "34563456",
            1000,
            "3456"
        ],
        "answer": "3456"
    },
    {
        "question": "2201 students from Kansas State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2074,
            100,
            6222,
            4148
        ],
        "answer": 2074
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 16 kg of meat in a day. Kim 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            10,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donaldson has Rs 3498 with him. He wants to buy fig. One kg of fig costs Rs 47. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of fig?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Meadows has Rs 3865 with him. He wants to buy apple. One kg of apple costs Rs 48. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of apple?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ritter has Rs 2971 with him. He wants to buy tomato. One kg of tomato costs Rs 16. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of tomato?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pearls",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            1000000,
            10
        ],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "grass",
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Esparza 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7865 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 23 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 23*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Gilbert 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6508 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 14 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 14*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or rat ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 853?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "visiting cards"
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6136. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            511.3333333333333,
            1022.6666666666666,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 511.3333333333333
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Lloyd 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8657. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 6 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2885.6666666666665,
            30000,
            1442.8333333333333,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1442.8333333333333
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry bought a phone which costed 8006 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 654 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            54,
            12,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "42598",
                "17034"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "42598",
            "17034"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "38965",
                "20667"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "38965",
            "20667"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than measuring cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman bought a phone which costed 6347 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 986 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            82,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 14 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 674 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 22 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            616,
            2,
            308
        ],
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "39603",
                "20029"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "39603",
            "20029"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 326 quince. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 76 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Krueger 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallegos bought a phone which costed 7825 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 561 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            46,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than plate. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "crayons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 352 potatoes. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 42 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            8,
            16,
            24,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "49967",
                "9665"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "49967",
            "9665"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 846,
        "question": "Jessie bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 14 meters, 11 meters, 23 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1692,
            846
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 17 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 961 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 29 tanks?",
        "options": [
            493,
            0,
            986,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 493
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Gaines 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8084 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 32 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 32*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Krueger 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1137,
        "question": "Lawson bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 8 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1137,
            1034.5,
            0,
            2274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Mary 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6371. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            796.375,
            30000,
            1592.75,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 796.375
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Flynn in Delaware for 1 month = 5384. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            389,
            "5384"
        ],
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Gaines 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6984 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 29*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "salt",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Morgan in Arkansas for 1 month = 2829. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            689,
            "2829"
        ],
        "answer": 689
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hebert bought a phone which costed 6076 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 591 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            6,
            2,
            0,
            48
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "answer": 1811,
        "question": "Rich bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 9 meters, 37 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1811,
            0,
            3622,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than glass. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 238 dollars of its actual cost which is 620 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 32 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            7616,
            0,
            15232
        ],
        "answer": 7616
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "bobby pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 234 dragonfruit. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 100 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 61, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            921,
            46,
            "61"
        ],
        "answer": 921
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Donovan in Guam for 1 month = 15737. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "15737",
            375
        ],
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            2500,
            5000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "2500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Chervy in West Virginia for 1 month = 2107. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "2107",
            926,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 926
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than bottle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 12 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 564 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 19 tanks?",
        "options": [
            456,
            0,
            2,
            228
        ],
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1250,
            1000000,
            2500
        ],
        "answer": "1250"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            200,
            400
        ],
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable plates",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "57596",
                "2036"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "57596",
            "2036"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 1977,
        "question": "Gaines bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 16 meters, 11 meters, 40 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1977,
            3954,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 757?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts has Rs 1958 with him. He wants to buy boysenberry. One kg of boysenberry costs Rs 22. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of boysenberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jennings has Rs 4270 with him. He wants to buy raspberry. One kg of raspberry costs Rs 18. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of raspberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            500,
            250,
            0,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 321 dollars of its actual cost which is 747 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 53 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            17013,
            34026,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 17013
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5053. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            1010.6,
            505.3
        ],
        "answer": 505.3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 434, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            "434",
            37,
            924
        ],
        "answer": 924
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 595?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5510. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            1102.0,
            2204.0,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1102.0
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 3 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 9 months ?",
        "options": [
            "243",
            1000,
            "243243243",
            "243243"
        ],
        "answer": "243"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Cox 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            10,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Schmitt 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 488 dollars of its actual cost which is 939 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 60 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            58560,
            29280,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 29280
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 139 olive. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 60 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Valenzuela in Puerto Rico for 1 month = 9481. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "9481",
            50000,
            907
        ],
        "answer": 907
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than tin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "safety pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 847?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 586?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 22 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 2 months ?",
        "options": [
            "396",
            "396396",
            1000,
            "396396396"
        ],
        "answer": "396"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than measuring cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons",
            "visiting cards"
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            800,
            1000000,
            400
        ],
        "answer": "400"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7762. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 3 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            2587.3333333333335,
            5174.666666666667,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2587.3333333333335
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 2 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            "216216",
            "216216216",
            1000,
            "216"
        ],
        "answer": "216"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than juicer. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "crayons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Clarke has Rs 3998 with him. He wants to buy blood orange. One kg of blood orange costs Rs 42. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of blood orange?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 253, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            5,
            742,
            "253",
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 742
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "4082 students from Georgia State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            6298,
            9447,
            3149,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3149
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chervy bought a phone which costed 9846 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 657 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            54,
            0,
            16,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 128 lime. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 66 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermocol balls",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 480 plum. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 34 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            14,
            28,
            42,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 112, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            690,
            "can be anything",
            "112",
            7
        ],
        "answer": 690
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 371 dollars of its actual cost which is 925 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 46 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            34132,
            0,
            17066,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 17066
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "crayons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "3911",
                "55721"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "3911",
            "55721"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "wall pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd has Rs 2683 with him. He wants to buy tamarillo. One kg of tamarillo costs Rs 39. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of tamarillo?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry has Rs 534 with him. He wants to buy currant. One kg of currant costs Rs 17. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of currant?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 35 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 830 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 19 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1330,
            665
        ],
        "answer": 665
    },
    {
        "question": "Tom took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5299. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1059.8,
            0,
            30000,
            2119.6
        ],
        "answer": 1059.8
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 40 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            "43204320",
            "432043204320",
            "4320",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "4320"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            50,
            0,
            100
        ],
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Brooks in Colorado for 1 month = 4997. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "4997",
            50000,
            85
        ],
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or dog ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 109, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            28,
            882,
            "109",
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 882
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "thermocol"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mcgrath 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6843 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 27 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 27*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable glasses",
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 400 loquat. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 100 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 483, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            589,
            0,
            "can be anything",
            "483"
        ],
        "answer": 589
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Oconnor in Alabama for 1 month = 7481. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "7481",
            231
        ],
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            20000,
            1000000,
            10000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "10000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Rice in West Virginia for 1 month = 4798. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            780,
            50000,
            "4798"
        ],
        "answer": 780
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 273 lychee. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 76 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1925,
        "question": "Freeman bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 15 meters, 40 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            3850,
            1925
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 439, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            44,
            800,
            "439"
        ],
        "answer": 800
    },
    {
        "answer": 1638,
        "question": "Mcgrath bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 10 meters, 37 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            1638,
            0,
            3276
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 54, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            30,
            "can be anything",
            "54",
            527
        ],
        "answer": 527
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "2247 students from Wisconsin State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4144,
            6216,
            100,
            2072
        ],
        "answer": 2072
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Donaldson 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5560 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 40 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 40*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            16,
            32,
            0,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Gaines in Illinois for 1 month = 13361. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            890,
            50000,
            "13361"
        ],
        "answer": 890
    },
    {
        "question": "1378 students from Kentucky State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1200,
            800,
            400
        ],
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "1549 students from Oregon State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            739,
            2217,
            1478,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 739
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "10658",
                "48974"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "10658",
            "48974"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 46 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            "41404140",
            "4140",
            1000,
            "414041404140"
        ],
        "answer": "4140"
    },
    {
        "question": "4704 students from South Carolina State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3621,
            7242,
            10863,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3621
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "3963 students from Arizona State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            9735,
            6490,
            3245,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3245
    },
    {
        "question": "2469 students from Michigan State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            6390,
            2130,
            4260
        ],
        "answer": 2130
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 280, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            631,
            14,
            "280"
        ],
        "answer": 631
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Crosby bought a phone which costed 6450 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 728 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            60,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            160,
            80,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 28 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1260",
            1000,
            "126012601260",
            "12601260"
        ],
        "answer": "1260"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            16,
            1000000,
            8
        ],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd bought a phone which costed 6529 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 722 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            60,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 434 dollars of its actual cost which is 879 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 39 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            33852,
            2,
            0,
            16926
        ],
        "answer": 16926
    },
    {
        "question": "If 16 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 943 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 13 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            208,
            416,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mcgrath 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9721 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 33 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 33*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Bradford 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9808 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 39 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 39*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "7577",
                "52055"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "7577",
            "52055"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 187 dollars of its actual cost which is 958 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 60 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            11220,
            22440,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 11220
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "foam",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Potts 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5913 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 37 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 37*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 271 tomato. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 76 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than pan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 282 strawberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 73 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "shells",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "stem barks",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 241, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            50,
            "241",
            992
        ],
        "answer": 992
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stein took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6974. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 1 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            6974.0,
            0,
            13948.0
        ],
        "answer": 6974.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Esparza has Rs 3624 with him. He wants to buy tomatoes. One kg of tomatoes costs Rs 43. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of tomatoes?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce has Rs 3095 with him. He wants to buy pineapple. One kg of pineapple costs Rs 33. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of pineapple?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 392 dollars of its actual cost which is 693 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 37 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            29008,
            0,
            14504,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 14504
    },
    {
        "question": "Gaines has Rs 2032 with him. He wants to buy quince. One kg of quince costs Rs 23. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of quince?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts has Rs 4277 with him. He wants to buy shrimp. One kg of shrimp costs Rs 49. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of shrimp?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "chilli flakes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "1885 students from Louisiana State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4902,
            3268,
            1634,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1634
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "44795",
                "14837"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "44795",
            "14837"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Krueger in Texas for 1 month = 17769. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "17769",
            50000,
            335
        ],
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": 2051,
        "question": "Buckley bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 13 meters, 39 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            4102,
            1034.5,
            2051
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 265, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            740,
            "265",
            25
        ],
        "answer": 740
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford bought a phone which costed 6701 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 563 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            46,
            0,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr has Rs 3715 with him. He wants to buy tamarillo. One kg of tamarillo costs Rs 26. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of tamarillo?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "If 30 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 915 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 27 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            1620,
            810,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 810
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tom has Rs 4107 with him. He wants to buy currant. One kg of currant costs Rs 43. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of currant?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "lollipops",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "Crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than bowl. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9900. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 1 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            19800.0,
            9900.0,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 9900.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 345 dollars of its actual cost which is 820 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 44 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            30360,
            15180,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 15180
    },
    {
        "question": "Bridges has Rs 4983 with him. He wants to buy jackfruit. One kg of jackfruit costs Rs 37. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of jackfruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "3783 students from West Virginia State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            11241,
            7494,
            3747,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3747
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1101,
        "question": "Jennings bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 5 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2202,
            1034.5,
            1101,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "1081 students from Mississippi State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            724,
            2172,
            1448
        ],
        "answer": 724
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Gaines 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            12,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "41096",
                "18536"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "41096",
            "18536"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hogan bought a phone which costed 5363 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 821 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            33,
            68,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1149,
        "question": "Jessie bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 14 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1149,
            1034.5,
            2298
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "sugar",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "foam",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 158 banana. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 61 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "1814 students from Oregon State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1162,
            100,
            1743,
            581
        ],
        "answer": 581
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 33 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "14851485",
            "148514851485",
            "1485",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1485"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bridges has Rs 1755 with him. He wants to buy salal berry. One kg of salal berry costs Rs 45. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of salal berry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1250,
            625,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "625"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "2151 students from Ohio State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            666,
            100,
            1332,
            1998
        ],
        "answer": 666
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            1250,
            2500
        ],
        "answer": "1250"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 180 dollars of its actual cost which is 942 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 20 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            7200,
            3600
        ],
        "answer": 3600
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 22 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "594",
            "594594594",
            "594594"
        ],
        "answer": "594"
    },
    {
        "question": "Webster has Rs 2254 with him. He wants to buy date. One kg of date costs Rs 30. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of date?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks has Rs 4630 with him. He wants to buy persimmon. One kg of persimmon costs Rs 22. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of persimmon?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 216?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "3875",
                "55757"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "3875",
            "55757"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "foam",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 34 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "36723672",
            "3672",
            "367236723672"
        ],
        "answer": "3672"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 831?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 45 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            "405405",
            "405405405",
            "405",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "405"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley bought a phone which costed 6310 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 859 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            23,
            70,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moyer took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7181. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 2 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            3590.5,
            7181.0,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 3590.5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moyer took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6962. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            580.1666666666666,
            1160.3333333333333,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 580.1666666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bobby pins",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1838,
        "question": "Meadows bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 15 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1838,
            3676,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermocol balls",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Mccoy 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7853 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 20 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 20*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Flynn has Rs 2089 with him. He wants to buy shrimp. One kg of shrimp costs Rs 26. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of shrimp?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": 1446,
        "question": "Valentine bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 10 meters, 35 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1446,
            0,
            2892,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 285?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            4000,
            0,
            2000
        ],
        "answer": "2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Freeman 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            38,
            0,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than saucepan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "sugar",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "45667",
                "13965"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "45667",
            "13965"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 233 dollars of its actual cost which is 990 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 53 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            24698,
            0,
            12349,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 12349
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 25 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "15751575",
            "1575",
            "157515751575"
        ],
        "answer": "1575"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 33 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 799 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 13 tanks?",
        "options": [
            858,
            0,
            2,
            429
        ],
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 617?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "21155",
                "38477"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "21155",
            "38477"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 26 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            "936936936",
            1000,
            "936",
            "936936"
        ],
        "answer": "936"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stein has Rs 4647 with him. He wants to buy kiwi fruit. One kg of kiwi fruit costs Rs 27. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of kiwi fruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            400,
            200,
            0,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "27823",
                "31809"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "27823",
            "31809"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 179 huckleberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 78 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3386 students from Montana State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            5880,
            2940,
            8820
        ],
        "answer": 2940
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "31692",
                "27940"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "31692",
            "27940"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 25 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            "900",
            "900900900",
            "900900",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "900"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "4674 students from Nebraska State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5956,
            8934,
            100,
            2978
        ],
        "answer": 2978
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce bought a phone which costed 5731 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 799 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            66,
            3,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable glasses",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 115, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            23,
            "115",
            779
        ],
        "answer": 779
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "wall pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Carr in Kentucky for 1 month = 10831. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            253,
            "10831"
        ],
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 17 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 552 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 15 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            510,
            255
        ],
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 42 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            "3780",
            1000,
            "37803780",
            "378037803780"
        ],
        "answer": "3780"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Kim 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7617 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 27 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 27*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 23 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 523 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 29 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1334,
            667,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 667
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bright in Massachusetts for 1 month = 2423. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "2423",
            50000,
            379
        ],
        "answer": 379
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "visiting cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Mary 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            40,
            3,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than saucepan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman bought a phone which costed 8554 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 560 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            46,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than measuring cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath has Rs 3797 with him. He wants to buy boysenberry. One kg of boysenberry costs Rs 19. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of boysenberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "45910",
                "13722"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "45910",
            "13722"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            80,
            40,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "47171",
                "12461"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "47171",
            "12461"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "bobby pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stout took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5200. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            520.0,
            1040.0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 520.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Valentine bought a phone which costed 6480 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 789 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            13,
            64,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Hebert in Guam for 1 month = 7165. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "7165",
            50000,
            377
        ],
        "answer": 377
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 318?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bobby pins",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Booker 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8184 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 36 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 36*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 294 dollars of its actual cost which is 694 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 39 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            11466,
            0,
            22932,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 11466
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 461 watermelon. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 63 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "2513 students from Wyoming State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2200,
            4400,
            6600,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2200
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "pearls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "3714 students from South Carolina State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            6462,
            9693,
            100,
            3231
        ],
        "answer": 3231
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than jar. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1001,
        "question": "Day bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 6 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            1001,
            2002,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 47 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 624 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 25 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2350,
            2,
            0,
            1175
        ],
        "answer": 1175
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gilbert took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8822. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 1 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            8822.0,
            17644.0,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 8822.0
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "14188",
                "45444"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "14188",
            "45444"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 34 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 740 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 25 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            850,
            1700
        ],
        "answer": 850
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than tumbler. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1250,
            625,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "625"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            500,
            0,
            1000000,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks bought a phone which costed 5137 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 930 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            76,
            37,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Rice in Palau for 1 month = 10110. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "10110",
            58,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than mug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Stout 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 495, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            19,
            "495",
            "can be anything",
            682
        ],
        "answer": 682
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "3650 students from Michigan State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4935,
            3290,
            1645,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1645
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary bought a phone which costed 6336 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 883 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            12,
            72
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 442, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            804,
            11,
            "442"
        ],
        "answer": 804
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins",
            "cookers"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Meadows 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8390 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 31 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 31*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Oconnor in Michigan for 1 month = 7450. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            319,
            "7450"
        ],
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1790,
        "question": "Conley bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 11 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3580,
            0,
            1034.5,
            1790
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Chervy 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6900 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 16 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 16*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Esparza 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6616 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 28 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 28*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7175. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            652.2727272727273,
            0,
            1304.5454545454545
        ],
        "answer": 652.2727272727273
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "polythene covers",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "socks",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley has Rs 2873 with him. He wants to buy mandarine. One kg of mandarine costs Rs 30. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of mandarine?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 711?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Serrano has Rs 1176 with him. He wants to buy blackberry. One kg of blackberry costs Rs 26. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of blackberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary bought a phone which costed 9274 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 946 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            78,
            2,
            0,
            29
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton",
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 250 dollars of its actual cost which is 963 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 48 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            12000,
            24000,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 12000
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Clarke in Texas for 1 month = 4256. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "4256",
            50000,
            104
        ],
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "23006",
                "36626"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "23006",
            "36626"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 1041,
        "question": "Bruce bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 14 meters, 22 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1041,
            2082,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Gallegos in Maryland for 1 month = 6393. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "6393",
            5
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 13 kg of meat in a day. Henry 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Harry in Massachusetts for 1 month = 14475. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "14475",
            851
        ],
        "answer": 851
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 322, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "322",
            708,
            15,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 708
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            100,
            200,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glue sticks",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 282 pomelo. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 98 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 106?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bridges has Rs 1823 with him. He wants to buy passionfruit. One kg of passionfruit costs Rs 35. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of passionfruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tea kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 112 dollars of its actual cost which is 749 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 70 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            7840,
            15680,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 7840
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Fin whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "57802",
                "1830"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "57802",
            "1830"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "45222",
                "14410"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "45222",
            "14410"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Henry 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            1,
            12,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley has Rs 4746 with him. He wants to buy kumquat. One kg of kumquat costs Rs 30. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of kumquat?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8496. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            772.3636363636364,
            0,
            30000,
            1544.7272727272727
        ],
        "answer": 772.3636363636364
    },
    {
        "question": "Conway bought a phone which costed 7301 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 544 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            44,
            18,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Moyer 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9382 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 38 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 38*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or cat ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Hess in Alabama for 1 month = 9748. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            182,
            "9748"
        ],
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "powder",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 174 blood orange. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 35 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 19 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 674 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            342,
            0,
            684,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "polythene covers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            50,
            1000000,
            0,
            100
        ],
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Hogan in Puerto Rico for 1 month = 1699. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "1699",
            861
        ],
        "answer": 861
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "thermocol",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ritter has Rs 194 with him. He wants to buy huckleberry. One kg of huckleberry costs Rs 26. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of huckleberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "2127 students from Florida State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1295,
            100,
            2590,
            3885
        ],
        "answer": 1295
    },
    {
        "answer": 1093,
        "question": "Stout bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 12 meters, 25 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1093,
            2186
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Kim in Alabama for 1 month = 12213. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            805,
            "12213",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 805
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "1488 students from Delaware State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3618,
            2412,
            100,
            1206
        ],
        "answer": 1206
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 7 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 2 months ?",
        "options": [
            "126126126",
            "126",
            "126126",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tumbler. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 347 dollars of its actual cost which is 941 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 50 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            34700,
            0,
            2,
            17350
        ],
        "answer": 17350
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "4707 students from Vermont State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            12954,
            8636,
            100,
            4318
        ],
        "answer": 4318
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable glasses",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 469, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "469",
            873,
            "can be anything",
            0
        ],
        "answer": 873
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 43 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 591 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            989,
            0,
            1978
        ],
        "answer": 989
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 14 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 694 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 29 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            406,
            812
        ],
        "answer": 406
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "polythene covers",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "48577",
                "11055"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "48577",
            "11055"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Meadows 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "tree leaves",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 416 dollars of its actual cost which is 870 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 28 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            11648,
            0,
            23296,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 11648
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Charles 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8973 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 37 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 37*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "pearls",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 551?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 964,
        "question": "Mike bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 8 meters, 24 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1928,
            1034.5,
            0,
            964
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts bought a phone which costed 9768 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 963 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            80,
            0,
            2,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1637,
        "question": "Valenzuela bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 9 meters, 34 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1034.5,
            3274,
            1637
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 245 avocado. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 33 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hogan has Rs 2602 with him. He wants to buy olive. One kg of olive costs Rs 24. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of olive?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "1093 students from Washington State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2304,
            768,
            100,
            1536
        ],
        "answer": 768
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 631?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 35 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 960 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            420,
            840,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than tiffin box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 953,
        "question": "Bright bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 10 meters, 23 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            953,
            1034.5,
            0,
            1906
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 950,
        "question": "York bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 11 meters, 27 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            950,
            1900,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 1 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            "9",
            "99",
            1000,
            "999"
        ],
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Conway 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Serrano bought a phone which costed 8534 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 865 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            72,
            14,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "paper clips",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Webster 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            38,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Fleming 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1729,
        "question": "Ashley bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 12 meters, 36 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1729,
            0,
            1034.5,
            3458
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Hess 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5396 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 32 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 32*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 12 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "10801080",
            "1080",
            "108010801080"
        ],
        "answer": "1080"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            400,
            200,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 140?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            2500,
            5000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "2500"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bright took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7765. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 7 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1109.2857142857142,
            0,
            30000,
            2218.5714285714284
        ],
        "answer": 1109.2857142857142
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 50 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 800 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 15 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1500,
            750,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 750
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 24 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 799 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 28 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1344,
            2,
            672,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 672
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Ford 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6059 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 14 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 14*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than blender. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Potts has Rs 418 with him. He wants to buy satsuma. One kg of satsuma costs Rs 25. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of satsuma?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Carr 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            1250,
            2500,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "1250"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1149,
        "question": "Bruce bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 14 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1034.5,
            2298,
            1149
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 963?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "answer": 964,
        "question": "Jessie bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 12 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1034.5,
            964,
            1928
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "3431 students from Guam State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1804,
            5412,
            3608,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1804
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bridges took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6720. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 3 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2240.0,
            0,
            4480.0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 2240.0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 374, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            790,
            "374",
            6,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 790
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 402 dollars of its actual cost which is 856 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 27 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            10854,
            2,
            21708,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 10854
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            5000,
            10000
        ],
        "answer": "5000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "York has Rs 2155 with him. He wants to buy blueberry. One kg of blueberry costs Rs 19. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of blueberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers",
            "visiting cards"
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ritter bought a phone which costed 7826 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 829 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            68,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Valenzuela bought a phone which costed 7916 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 632 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            52,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "3479 students from Texas State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4600,
            2300,
            6900,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2300
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Freeman 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8040 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 40 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 40*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "candies"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 422 bilberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 30 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            14,
            28,
            42,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than tea kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1035,
        "question": "Kim bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 11 meters, 25 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2070,
            1034.5,
            1035,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 17 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 6 months ?",
        "options": [
            "918",
            1000,
            "918918",
            "918918918"
        ],
        "answer": "918"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 356 dollars of its actual cost which is 666 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 23 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            16376,
            2,
            8188
        ],
        "answer": 8188
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Curry 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9425 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 20 hens of his village for which he will be paid 5 for each per day. Now he earns 20*5*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry bought a phone which costed 7338 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 732 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            60,
            30,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallegos bought a phone which costed 6036 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 511 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            16,
            2,
            0,
            42
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tiffin box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "5748",
                "53884"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "5748",
            "53884"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 16 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 597 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            480,
            0,
            960,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 480
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 441 lychee. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 92 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 144 dollars of its actual cost which is 859 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 31 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            4464,
            0,
            2,
            8928
        ],
        "answer": 4464
    },
    {
        "answer": 1619,
        "question": "Flynn bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 13 meters, 35 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3238,
            0,
            1619,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than kitchen dustbin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than measuring cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "small diamonds",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sims took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6312. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            1147.6363636363637,
            573.8181818181819,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 573.8181818181819
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 33 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            "3564",
            1000,
            "35643564",
            "356435643564"
        ],
        "answer": "3564"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 469 dollars of its actual cost which is 919 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 68 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            31892,
            0,
            63784,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 31892
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Schaefer took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6705. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2682.0,
            30000,
            1341.0
        ],
        "answer": 1341.0
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 38 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "23942394",
            "2394",
            "239423942394"
        ],
        "answer": "2394"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 16 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            "144144",
            "144",
            1000,
            "144144144"
        ],
        "answer": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "pepper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry bought a phone which costed 6996 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 638 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            52,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "visiting cards"
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 54?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stein took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7455. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            621.25,
            1242.5,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 621.25
    },
    {
        "answer": 1449,
        "question": "Tom bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 5 meters, 32 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1449,
            2898
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "flowers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "45263",
                "14369"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "45263",
            "14369"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "36260",
                "23372"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "36260",
            "23372"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 33 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            "297",
            "297297",
            1000,
            "297297297"
        ],
        "answer": "297"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath has Rs 2080 with him. He wants to buy apple. One kg of apple costs Rs 31. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of apple?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 38 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 625 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 17 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            646,
            2,
            1292
        ],
        "answer": 646
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "sugar",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "3773",
                "55859"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "3773",
            "55859"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Valenzuela has Rs 1480 with him. He wants to buy feijoa. One kg of feijoa costs Rs 27. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of feijoa?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 11 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 915 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            253,
            506,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "3560 students from Indiana State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3616,
            100,
            5424,
            1808
        ],
        "answer": 1808
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Krueger 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "lollipops",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bruce in Nebraska for 1 month = 14173. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "14173",
            93,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "answer": 1217,
        "question": "Freeman bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 14 meters, 30 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            1217,
            0,
            2434
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bobby pins",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moyer bought a phone which costed 7582 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 945 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            78,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 267 kumquat. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 40 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Freeman 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "visiting card",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallegos took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8550. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2137.5,
            1068.75,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1068.75
    },
    {
        "answer": 1249,
        "question": "Warren bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 5 meters, 30 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2498,
            1249,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 383 rambutan. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 66 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            15,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "tumblers",
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Duarte 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8036 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 38 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 38*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Stein 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5213 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 15 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 15*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 28 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 798 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 16 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            448,
            896
        ],
        "answer": 448
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ribbons",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 865?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 2 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "126",
            "126126",
            "126126126"
        ],
        "answer": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bobby pins",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            16,
            1000000,
            8,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 49 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 697 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2940,
            2,
            1470,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1470
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable glasses"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 207?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 19 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "684",
            "684684684",
            "684684"
        ],
        "answer": "684"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            32,
            0,
            16,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 67, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            45,
            "can be anything",
            "67",
            715
        ],
        "answer": 715
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 39 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 2 months ?",
        "options": [
            "702702",
            "702702702",
            1000,
            "702"
        ],
        "answer": "702"
    },
    {
        "answer": 854,
        "question": "Booker bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 15 meters, 23 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1708,
            1034.5,
            854,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 390 blackcurrant. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 81 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            2500,
            1250
        ],
        "answer": "1250"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 305 dollars of its actual cost which is 986 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 45 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            27450,
            0,
            13725
        ],
        "answer": 13725
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than jug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 11 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "693",
            1000,
            "693693693",
            "693693"
        ],
        "answer": "693"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 39 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 576 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 17 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1326,
            663,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 663
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moyer took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7789. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1416.1818181818182,
            708.0909090909091,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 708.0909090909091
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 39?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "gift wraps",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Klein in Texas for 1 month = 3589. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "3589",
            79,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "puffed rice",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "visiting cards",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gilbert has Rs 2086 with him. He wants to buy mandarine. One kg of mandarine costs Rs 21. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of mandarine?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 130 date. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 39 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1274,
        "question": "Warren bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 12 meters, 29 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            2548,
            0,
            1274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Conway 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6261 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 29*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Donaldson in Massachusetts for 1 month = 14664. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            471,
            50000,
            "14664"
        ],
        "answer": 471
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1005,
        "question": "Potts bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 11 meters, 22 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1005,
            1034.5,
            0,
            2010
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gilbert bought a phone which costed 7106 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 764 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            31,
            0,
            2,
            62
        ],
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conway has Rs 3144 with him. He wants to buy cucumber. One kg of cucumber costs Rs 21. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of cucumber?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Hogan in Oklahoma for 1 month = 13980. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            908,
            50000,
            "13980"
        ],
        "answer": 908
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 166 physalis. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 72 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5956. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 6 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            992.6666666666666,
            30000,
            1985.3333333333333
        ],
        "answer": 992.6666666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman has Rs 240 with him. He wants to buy blueberry. One kg of blueberry costs Rs 31. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of blueberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 22 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 918 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 19 tanks?",
        "options": [
            836,
            2,
            0,
            418
        ],
        "answer": 418
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 270 dragonfruit. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 67 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Conway bought a phone which costed 6964 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 823 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            68,
            34,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 141 dollars of its actual cost which is 823 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 33 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            9306,
            4653
        ],
        "answer": 4653
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 134, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            921,
            "134",
            18
        ],
        "answer": 921
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bridges in Montana for 1 month = 15152. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "15152",
            50000,
            871
        ],
        "answer": 871
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            800,
            400
        ],
        "answer": "400"
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5328. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2664.0,
            30000,
            1332.0,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1332.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bruce in Alabama for 1 month = 1070. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            708,
            "1070"
        ],
        "answer": 708
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 151 dollars of its actual cost which is 637 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 35 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            10570,
            2,
            5285
        ],
        "answer": 5285
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 308 apricot. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 79 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Ashley 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            38,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 384?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "paper",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than tin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5711. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1427.75,
            30000,
            2855.5
        ],
        "answer": 1427.75
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 10 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            "900900900",
            1000,
            "900900",
            "900"
        ],
        "answer": "900"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "2001 students from Hawaii State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5823,
            3882,
            1941,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1941
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chervy has Rs 488 with him. He wants to buy strawberry. One kg of strawberry costs Rs 20. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of strawberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "keys",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gilbert took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8681. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 6 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            1446.8333333333333,
            0,
            2893.6666666666665
        ],
        "answer": 1446.8333333333333
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 150, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "150",
            26,
            "can be anything",
            507
        ],
        "answer": 507
    },
    {
        "question": "Li bought a phone which costed 6634 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 648 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            54,
            2,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "puffed rice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 241?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 433, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            35,
            "433",
            "can be anything",
            770
        ],
        "answer": 770
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than blender. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "nails",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "18379",
                "41253"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "18379",
            "41253"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            25,
            0,
            50
        ],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8422. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            765.6363636363636,
            1531.2727272727273,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 765.6363636363636
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6511. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            651.1,
            1302.2
        ],
        "answer": 651.1
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than bottle cap. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conway has Rs 652 with him. He wants to buy strawberry. One kg of strawberry costs Rs 44. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of strawberry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 3 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 12 months ?",
        "options": [
            "324324324",
            "324324",
            "324",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "324"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 126 dollars of its actual cost which is 953 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 45 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            11340,
            0,
            5670,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 5670
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            200,
            1000000,
            400
        ],
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than tin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 927?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "grass",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 20 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1800",
            "180018001800",
            "18001800",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1800"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bradford took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8636. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1727.2,
            0,
            30000,
            863.6
        ],
        "answer": 863.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "3244 students from Hawaii State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            559,
            1118,
            1677,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 559
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Curry has Rs 1368 with him. He wants to buy cucumber. One kg of cucumber costs Rs 25. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of cucumber?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 16 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "11521152",
            1000,
            "1152",
            "115211521152"
        ],
        "answer": "1152"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pearls"
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 220, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "220",
            "can be anything",
            865,
            42
        ],
        "answer": 865
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Potts 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9418 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 25 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 25*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 22 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 740 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 28 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1232,
            2,
            0,
            616
        ],
        "answer": 616
    },
    {
        "question": "Donaldson bought a phone which costed 6303 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 682 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            23,
            2,
            56,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "hairbands",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 372 dollars of its actual cost which is 884 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 20 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            14880,
            0,
            7440
        ],
        "answer": 7440
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 13 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 710 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 20 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            520,
            260
        ],
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than spoon. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 34 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            "918918918",
            1000,
            "918918",
            "918"
        ],
        "answer": "918"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            4000,
            1000000,
            0,
            2000
        ],
        "answer": "2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than small tub. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "thermocol balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Chervy 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7774 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 26 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 26*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "visiting cards",
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 20 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 1 months ?",
        "options": [
            "180",
            1000,
            "180180180",
            "180180"
        ],
        "answer": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath bought a phone which costed 5216 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 851 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            11,
            70
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1381,
        "question": "Bridges bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 16 meters, 6 meters, 33 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1034.5,
            2762,
            1381
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 21 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "945945945",
            "945",
            "945945"
        ],
        "answer": "945"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1706,
        "question": "Kim bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 9 meters, 35 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1706,
            3412,
            1034.5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Green anaconda",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            160,
            80
        ],
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1545,
        "question": "Day bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 20 meters, 11 meters, 32 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3090,
            1034.5,
            1545,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 301 dollars of its actual cost which is 970 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 60 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            36120,
            2,
            18060
        ],
        "answer": 18060
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "2406 students from Pennsylvania State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            854,
            100,
            1708,
            2562
        ],
        "answer": 854
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Day 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 555?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1865,
        "question": "Stout bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 12 meters, 40 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1865,
            1034.5,
            3730
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "ATM cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 27 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 662 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 19 tanks?",
        "options": [
            513,
            0,
            1026,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 513
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 276 mango. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 77 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 341 dollars of its actual cost which is 794 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 32 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            21824,
            0,
            10912
        ],
        "answer": 10912
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Day 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5704 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 16 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 16*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 313, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            "313",
            512,
            42
        ],
        "answer": 512
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermocol balls"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "bones"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "wall pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 25 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 639 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 24 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            600,
            1200
        ],
        "answer": 600
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 353 mulberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 53 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 182 lime. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 84 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "answer": 950,
        "question": "Schaefer bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 10 meters, 25 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1900,
            950
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 105 dollars of its actual cost which is 906 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 32 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3360,
            2,
            6720
        ],
        "answer": 3360
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleming bought a phone which costed 7827 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 985 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            37,
            2,
            82
        ],
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than plate. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Lloyd in Michigan for 1 month = 4928. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            558,
            "4928"
        ],
        "answer": 558
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "23861",
                "35771"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "23861",
            "35771"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Potts in Vermont for 1 month = 10686. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            734,
            50000,
            "10686"
        ],
        "answer": 734
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "thermocol"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1704,
        "question": "Conley bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 14 meters, 8 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3408,
            0,
            1034.5,
            1704
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than blender. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 229 date. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 62 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "If 33 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 963 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 25 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            825,
            1650,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 825
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Hebert 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1000000,
            2000
        ],
        "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "47625",
                "12007"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "47625",
            "12007"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than small tub. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren has Rs 2462 with him. He wants to buy star fruit. One kg of star fruit costs Rs 45. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of star fruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "42148",
                "17484"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "42148",
            "17484"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "1142 students from Arizona State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            856,
            428,
            100,
            1284
        ],
        "answer": 428
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "bobby pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1054,
        "question": "Sims bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 15 meters, 27 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            0,
            1054,
            2108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than juicer. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 401 guava. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 37 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            10,
            20,
            30,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "safety pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 21 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "945945945",
            "945",
            "945945"
        ],
        "answer": "945"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8876. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            0,
            739.6666666666666,
            1479.3333333333333
        ],
        "answer": 739.6666666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7384. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 7 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            0,
            2109.714285714286,
            1054.857142857143
        ],
        "answer": 1054.857142857143
    },
    {
        "question": "Blanchard bought a phone which costed 6337 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 649 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            54,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tea cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "tumblers",
            "feather",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 347 dollars of its actual cost which is 614 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 24 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            16656,
            8328,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 8328
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 444 dollars of its actual cost which is 829 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 51 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            45288,
            2,
            22644,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 22644
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 773?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates",
            "glue sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1137,
        "question": "Mary bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 14 meters, 10 meters, 29 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1034.5,
            1137,
            2274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 464 guava. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 62 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            80,
            40
        ],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 44 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 611 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 25 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2200,
            2,
            0,
            1100
        ],
        "answer": 1100
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "lollipops",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Ritter in Virgin Islands for 1 month = 15096. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "15096",
            50000,
            883
        ],
        "answer": 883
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Mary 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8288 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 36 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 36*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "grass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Webster bought a phone which costed 5204 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 963 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            28,
            80,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 63?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Ritter 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7488 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 35 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 35*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Serrano in Wisconsin for 1 month = 19319. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            484,
            "19319"
        ],
        "answer": 484
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than small tub. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "Sperm whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than oil can . true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1205,
        "question": "Li bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 9 meters, 32 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1205,
            0,
            1034.5,
            2410
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "3926 students from Rhode Island State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            7704,
            2568,
            5136,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2568
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "glue sticks",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "Alaskan Moose\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            625,
            0,
            1250,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "625"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 134?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6084. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 6 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            0,
            2028.0,
            1014.0
        ],
        "answer": 1014.0
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tamarind",
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 149, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            "149",
            16,
            800
        ],
        "answer": 800
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "hairbands",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1118,
        "question": "Duarte bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 9 meters, 26 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2236,
            1034.5,
            1118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than bottle cap. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 451 dollars of its actual cost which is 660 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 29 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            26158,
            13079,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 13079
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "White rhinoceros\t"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Morgan in Illinois for 1 month = 19075. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "19075",
            50000,
            407
        ],
        "answer": 407
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 606?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Blanchard 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 277 strawberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 73 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            1250,
            2500
        ],
        "answer": "1250"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 30 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            "810",
            "810810810",
            "810810",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "810"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            400,
            800,
            0,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "400"
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren has Rs 163 with him. He wants to buy dragonfruit. One kg of dragonfruit costs Rs 48. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of dragonfruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Humpback whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard",
            "Elephant seal"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "crayons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 199 dollars of its actual cost which is 837 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 37 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            14726,
            7363
        ],
        "answer": 7363
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 279 dollars of its actual cost which is 648 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 31 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            8649,
            2,
            17298,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 8649
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 225 dollars of its actual cost which is 993 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 50 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            11250,
            22500,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 11250
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 375 dollars of its actual cost which is 615 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 25 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            18750,
            9375
        ],
        "answer": 9375
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "pencils"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than measuring cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable glasses",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than bottle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter",
            "flowers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "puffed rice",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 352 jambul. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 83 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 14 kg of meat in a day. Ruther 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            8,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 388 dollars of its actual cost which is 656 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 21 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            8148,
            2,
            16296
        ],
        "answer": 8148
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "thermocol"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Krueger 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6560 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 35 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 35*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "54169",
                "5463"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "54169",
            "5463"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than blender. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 302, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "302",
            0,
            737,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 737
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 311, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            969,
            26,
            "can be anything",
            "311"
        ],
        "answer": 969
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stress balls",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Valentine 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9865 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 20 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 20*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a York in New Mexico for 1 month = 1275. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            641,
            50000,
            "1275"
        ],
        "answer": 641
    },
    {
        "question": "Donovan has Rs 2532 with him. He wants to buy fish. One kg of fish costs Rs 35. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of fish?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 345, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            46,
            746,
            "345"
        ],
        "answer": 746
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "puffed rice",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "14324",
                "45308"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "14324",
            "45308"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Lloyd in Alaska for 1 month = 15450. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "15450",
            394
        ],
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            250,
            500
        ],
        "answer": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pencils",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "small diamonds",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            200,
            400,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 22 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            "217821782178",
            "21782178",
            1000,
            "2178"
        ],
        "answer": "2178"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 349, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "349",
            824,
            1,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 824
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 398, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            "398",
            538,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 538
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 380, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            704,
            "can be anything",
            4,
            "380"
        ],
        "answer": 704
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 422 dollars of its actual cost which is 713 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 48 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            20256,
            0,
            40512,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 20256
    },
    {
        "question": "1632 students from Massachusetts State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            3084,
            100,
            1028,
            2056
        ],
        "answer": 1028
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than tiffin box. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "4865 students from Louisiana State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            3300,
            9900,
            6600
        ],
        "answer": 3300
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley has Rs 2843 with him. He wants to buy salal berry. One kg of salal berry costs Rs 34. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of salal berry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "puffed rice",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 16 kg of meat in a day. Best 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            10,
            5,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "visiting cards"
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1445,
        "question": "Oconnor bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 14 meters, 32 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2890,
            1034.5,
            0,
            1445
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Schmitt took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6362. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1413.7777777777778,
            30000,
            706.8888888888889
        ],
        "answer": 706.8888888888889
    },
    {
        "answer": 1709,
        "question": "Jessie bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 11 meters, 38 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1709,
            1034.5,
            3418
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": 1149,
        "question": "Lawson bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 14 meters, 13 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1149,
            1034.5,
            0,
            2298
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kim took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7520. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1253.3333333333333,
            626.6666666666666,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 626.6666666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pearls",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "socks",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jennings has Rs 4183 with him. He wants to buy pomelo. One kg of pomelo costs Rs 36. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of pomelo?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "49550",
                "10082"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "49550",
            "10082"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 344, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            4,
            "can be anything",
            720,
            "344"
        ],
        "answer": 720
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Flynn 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9092 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 17 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 17*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "answer": 709,
        "question": "Ford bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 9 meters, 22 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            709,
            1418,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "51791",
                "7841"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "51791",
            "7841"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7465. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 1 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            14930.0,
            0,
            30000,
            7465.0
        ],
        "answer": 7465.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "candies",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "balloons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "visiting cards",
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mike bought a phone which costed 8846 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 910 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            21,
            74,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 309, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            31,
            763,
            "309",
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 763
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 457 avocado. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 40 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            11,
            22,
            33,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "answer": 806,
        "question": "Conway bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 13 meters, 14 meters, 21 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            806,
            1034.5,
            1612,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallegos took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9527. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 6 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            3175.6666666666665,
            0,
            30000,
            1587.8333333333333
        ],
        "answer": 1587.8333333333333
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 159, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            777,
            "can be anything",
            40,
            "159"
        ],
        "answer": 777
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cox took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5261. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 3 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            3507.3333333333335,
            1753.6666666666667
        ],
        "answer": 1753.6666666666667
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley bought a phone which costed 8390 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 747 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            26,
            62,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 441, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            557,
            13,
            "441"
        ],
        "answer": 557
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Stein 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Conley 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8190 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 21 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 21*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 263, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            36,
            "can be anything",
            "263",
            746
        ],
        "answer": 746
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 283 dollars of its actual cost which is 886 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 23 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            13018,
            0,
            2,
            6509
        ],
        "answer": 6509
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 859?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Jennings 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7284 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 6 for each per day. Now he earns 29*6*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 11 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 972 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 10 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            110,
            220
        ],
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "7689",
                "51943"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "7689",
            "51943"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "flowers",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "small diamonds",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            20,
            40
        ],
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 29 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "783",
            "783783783",
            "783783"
        ],
        "answer": "783"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "keys",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "grass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            5000,
            10000
        ],
        "answer": "5000"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "3193 students from Arizona State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1268,
            634,
            1902
        ],
        "answer": 634
    },
    {
        "question": "Duarte took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9260. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2057.777777777778,
            30000,
            1028.888888888889,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1028.888888888889
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "shells",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            16,
            1000000,
            32
        ],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "African forest elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 37 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            "2664",
            "266426642664",
            1000,
            "26642664"
        ],
        "answer": "2664"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "thermocol"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 10 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "270270",
            "270270270",
            "270"
        ],
        "answer": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than saucepan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than measuring cup. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "rice bag",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Bruce 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5204 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 23 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 23*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 347 cranberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 94 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 308 dollars of its actual cost which is 762 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 27 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            8316,
            0,
            2,
            16632
        ],
        "answer": 8316
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "small diamonds",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Giraffe"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 24 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 518 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 22 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1056,
            2,
            528
        ],
        "answer": 528
    },
    {
        "question": "3883 students from Idaho State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1438,
            2157,
            719
        ],
        "answer": 719
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sugar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 391, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "391",
            5,
            "can be anything",
            542
        ],
        "answer": 542
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moyer took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8859. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            0,
            4429.5,
            2214.75
        ],
        "answer": 2214.75
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or chilli flakes ?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "chilli flakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 390, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            660,
            "390",
            24,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 660
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Mccoy 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            10,
            0,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "40585",
                "19047"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "40585",
            "19047"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 174, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            856,
            "174",
            12,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 856
    },
    {
        "answer": 1125,
        "question": "Bridges bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 10 meters, 8 meters, 31 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1125,
            1034.5,
            0,
            2250
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "visiting cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "flowers",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 109 mulberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 41 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 20 kg of meat in a day. Booker 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            8,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 240 jujube. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 55 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "1777 students from Hawaii State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1599,
            100,
            3198,
            4797
        ],
        "answer": 1599
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Bradford 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce bought a phone which costed 5402 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 862 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            70,
            2,
            0,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Warner 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7270 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 15 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 15*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "safety pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "2218 students from Connecticut State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            6639,
            4426,
            2213
        ],
        "answer": 2213
    },
    {
        "question": "1804 students from Utah State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1118,
            2236,
            3354
        ],
        "answer": 1118
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1870,
        "question": "Oconnor bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 5 meters, 39 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            3740,
            0,
            1034.5,
            1870
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 246 lemon. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 67 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 411 dollars of its actual cost which is 698 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 45 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            18495,
            36990,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 18495
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 364 dollars of its actual cost which is 772 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 60 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            21840,
            0,
            2,
            43680
        ],
        "answer": 21840
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 314 dollars of its actual cost which is 796 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 64 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            40192,
            0,
            20096,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 20096
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "balloons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Clarke 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8849 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 10 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 10*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 489 mulberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 47 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            10,
            20,
            30,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 322 huckleberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 86 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "paper",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "11572",
                "48060"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "11572",
            "48060"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Cox in Kansas for 1 month = 2613. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "2613",
            50000,
            656
        ],
        "answer": 656
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Jessie 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5788 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 7 for each per day. Now he earns 29*7*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "powder",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or paper clips ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "paper clips",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "paper clips"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bones",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than bottle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone",
            "pearls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 13 kg of meat in a day. Schaefer 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "40179",
                "19453"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "40179",
            "19453"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            500,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "Crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9813. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 3 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3271.0,
            6542.0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 3271.0
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than plate. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 8 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 6 months ?",
        "options": [
            "432432432",
            "432",
            "432432",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "432"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 430, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            "430",
            35,
            809
        ],
        "answer": 809
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Klein in Missouri for 1 month = 8564. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "8564",
            375,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            5000,
            2500,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "2500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lizard",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "4573 students from District Of Columbia State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 2 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            7680,
            3840,
            100,
            11520
        ],
        "answer": 3840
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            40,
            0,
            20,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1793,
        "question": "Flynn bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 18 meters, 10 meters, 37 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3586,
            1034.5,
            1793
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than thermos flask. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ron bought a phone which costed 5922 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 521 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            11,
            0,
            42,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "4990 students from Virgin Islands State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            5655,
            100,
            1885,
            3770
        ],
        "answer": 1885
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Hess 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 99?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "crayons",
            "pumpkins"
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 884?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of keys . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "keys",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giraffe",
            "Pygmy Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Conway 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            0,
            100,
            50
        ],
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 304 dollars of its actual cost which is 903 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 61 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            18544,
            0,
            2,
            37088
        ],
        "answer": 18544
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7178. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 8 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            0,
            1794.5,
            897.25
        ],
        "answer": 897.25
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 12 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "118811881188",
            "1188",
            "11881188"
        ],
        "answer": "1188"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 48 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            "172817281728",
            1000,
            "17281728",
            "1728"
        ],
        "answer": "1728"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr bought a phone which costed 9423 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 737 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            60,
            0,
            2,
            28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 37 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            "13321332",
            1000,
            "133213321332",
            "1332"
        ],
        "answer": "1332"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 203 guava. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 76 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of glue sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "glue sticks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "cat"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Buckley 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5044 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 19 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 19*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mike has Rs 3934 with him. He wants to buy kiwi fruit. One kg of kiwi fruit costs Rs 29. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of kiwi fruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of cotton . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "cotton",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 806?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 279, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            764,
            "279",
            "can be anything",
            5
        ],
        "answer": 764
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Rice 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Fin whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Fin whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Miller took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9802. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            980.2,
            1960.4,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 980.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6427. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 7 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            918.1428571428571,
            0,
            1836.2857142857142
        ],
        "answer": 918.1428571428571
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "socks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Rich in Arkansas for 1 month = 19305. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            579,
            "19305"
        ],
        "answer": 579
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 105 dollars of its actual cost which is 688 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 27 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            2835,
            5670
        ],
        "answer": 2835
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jessie bought a phone which costed 7078 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 530 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            2,
            44
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "safety pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "kettles"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Schmitt 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5941 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 23 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 23*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Morgan in Oregon for 1 month = 17944. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            540,
            "17944"
        ],
        "answer": 540
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than kitchen dustbin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 223 bilberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 89 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "American bison",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "crayons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 315, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            23,
            "can be anything",
            "315",
            575
        ],
        "answer": 575
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "13179",
                "46453"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "13179",
            "46453"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 466?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 481, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            26,
            530,
            "can be anything",
            "481"
        ],
        "answer": 530
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "25518",
                "34114"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "25518",
            "34114"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "thermocol"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren has Rs 4537 with him. He wants to buy loquat. One kg of loquat costs Rs 47. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of loquat?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 45 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "44554455",
            "445544554455",
            "4455"
        ],
        "answer": "4455"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than kitchen dustbin. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "20534",
                "39098"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "20534",
            "39098"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons",
            "gift wraps"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "pots",
            "keys",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "candies",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 357 satsuma. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 59 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Donaldson bought a phone which costed 6891 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 718 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            3,
            2,
            0,
            58
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            1000000,
            200,
            0,
            100
        ],
        "answer": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or socks ?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "socks"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "pearls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 579?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "sugar",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 102 dollars of its actual cost which is 738 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 26 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            2652,
            5304
        ],
        "answer": 2652
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Stein 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            8,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Clarke in Puerto Rico for 1 month = 3877. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "3877",
            849,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 849
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bridges in Virgin Islands for 1 month = 12901. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "12901",
            50000,
            279
        ],
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "If 27 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 644 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            972,
            0,
            486
        ],
        "answer": 486
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Whale Shark",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            4,
            1000000,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Henry 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7991 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 29*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "24059",
                "35573"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "24059",
            "35573"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 35 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 582 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            630,
            1260,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 630
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "nails",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 410 apple. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 52 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "1189",
                "58443"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "1189",
            "58443"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 295 dollars of its actual cost which is 683 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 57 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            16815,
            0,
            2,
            33630
        ],
        "answer": 16815
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "hairbands",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleming bought a phone which costed 6199 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 557 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            13,
            46
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 14 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 10 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1260",
            1000,
            "12601260",
            "126012601260"
        ],
        "answer": "1260"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cat",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 21 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 992 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 16 tanks?",
        "options": [
            336,
            0,
            672,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 20 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 530 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 10 tanks?",
        "options": [
            400,
            0,
            2,
            200
        ],
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Stout 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7736 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 21 hens of his village for which he will be paid 4 for each per day. Now he earns 21*4*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or puffed rice ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "puffed rice",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "puffed rice"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "popsicle sticks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 856?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            50,
            25,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Flynn 's family consumes 2 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            10,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 12 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 504 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 27 tanks?",
        "options": [
            324,
            0,
            2,
            648
        ],
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than bottle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than cooking pot. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or nails ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "nails",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "nails"
    },
    {
        "answer": 2010,
        "question": "Webster bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 11 meters, 40 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            4020,
            0,
            2010,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "tree leaves",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sims took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9391. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1878.2,
            939.1,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 939.1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson has Rs 4224 with him. He wants to buy goji berry. One kg of goji berry costs Rs 34. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of goji berry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "ATM cards",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Freeman 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "rice bag",
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Day has Rs 3206 with him. He wants to buy salal berry. One kg of salal berry costs Rs 26. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of salal berry?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1000
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 600?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Sperm whale",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 419 dollars of its actual cost which is 671 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 54 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            45252,
            22626,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 22626
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African Elephant",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "tumblers",
            "stem barks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "powder",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "1524 students from Ohio State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1776,
            2664,
            888
        ],
        "answer": 888
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgan bought a phone which costed 9794 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 777 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            64,
            28,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Serrano 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            8,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 408 dollars of its actual cost which is 967 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 43 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            35088,
            2,
            0,
            17544
        ],
        "answer": 17544
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "kite",
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 103 dollars of its actual cost which is 976 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 27 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            5562,
            2781,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2781
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "pumpkins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "1100 students from Florida State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 6 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1834,
            2751,
            917
        ],
        "answer": 917
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 851,
        "question": "Ford bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 17 meters, 11 meters, 21 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            851,
            0,
            1702,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than plate. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "powder",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "visiting card",
            "butter",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than blender. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 317, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "317",
            831,
            "can be anything",
            6
        ],
        "answer": 831
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or powder ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "balloons",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "powder"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry has Rs 1889 with him. He wants to buy breadfruit. One kg of breadfruit costs Rs 16. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of breadfruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 13 kg of meat in a day. Ron 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Ford 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5373 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 30 hens of his village for which he will be paid 2 for each per day. Now he earns 30*2*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Green anaconda",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 25 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 796 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            600,
            300,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 439 dollars of its actual cost which is 990 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 53 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            46534,
            2,
            23267,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 23267
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cox has Rs 309 with him. He wants to buy star fruit. One kg of star fruit costs Rs 39. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of star fruit?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Krueger 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5808 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 22 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 22*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "keys",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 351, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            913,
            "351",
            37,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 913
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "thermocol balls"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 20 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 816 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 29 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            580,
            1160
        ],
        "answer": 580
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "bottles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "thermos flask",
            "tablets",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "flowers",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bright took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7166. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            796.2222222222222,
            30000,
            1592.4444444444443
        ],
        "answer": 796.2222222222222
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "4694 students from Alaska State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            8074,
            12111,
            100,
            4037
        ],
        "answer": 4037
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess bought a phone which costed 9890 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 519 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            6,
            42
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 400, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "400",
            905,
            5,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 905
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 238 cucumber. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 76 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 793?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley bought a phone which costed 8088 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 914 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            31,
            0,
            2,
            76
        ],
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than small tub. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "American bison"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian Guar",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "answer": 915,
        "question": "Best bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 5 meters, 23 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            1830,
            915,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 471, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            43,
            "can be anything",
            "471",
            916
        ],
        "answer": 916
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 131 apricot. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 90 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or glue sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "glue sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "glue sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than tea kettle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallegos has Rs 4144 with him. He wants to buy persimmon. One kg of persimmon costs Rs 30. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of persimmon?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            6,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "crayons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath bought a phone which costed 9987 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 820 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            68,
            31,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "1015 students from Arizona State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 4 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1436,
            718,
            100,
            2154
        ],
        "answer": 718
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "visiting cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1763,
        "question": "Tom bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 11 meters, 39 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1763,
            1034.5,
            0,
            3526
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 278 dollars of its actual cost which is 817 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 59 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            16402,
            0,
            32804
        ],
        "answer": 16402
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            1000000,
            8
        ],
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "feather",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pumpkins",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of polythene covers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "polythene covers",
            "pumpkin"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 157, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            924,
            "157",
            25
        ],
        "answer": 924
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley has Rs 2675 with him. He wants to buy olive. One kg of olive costs Rs 30. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of olive?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rat"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "polythene covers",
            "backpacks"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "cotton candy",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "pots",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "jackfruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Humpback whale",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "cat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "cookers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "pearls",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Henry in Alabama for 1 month = 15439. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "15439",
            33,
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cox took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7034. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 2 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            7034.0,
            3517.0,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 3517.0
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 198 chili pepper. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 75 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "visiting card",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or stem barks ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "stem barks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 50 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 861 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            1500,
            3000,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 1500
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "visiting card"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than bottle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Green anaconda or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Green anaconda"
        ],
        "answer": "Green anaconda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Clarke 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 7766 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 29 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 29*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "big stone",
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 136, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            12,
            "136",
            687
        ],
        "answer": 687
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Whale Shark or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Whale Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Whale Shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 13 kg of meat in a day. Ford 's family consumes 4 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            0,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or pearls ?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "pearls",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pearls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian Guar"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of foam . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hogan has Rs 2384 with him. He wants to buy bell pepper. One kg of bell pepper costs Rs 39. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of bell pepper?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            1,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Crosby 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5179 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 27 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 27*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cotton candy",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 30 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 5 months ?",
        "options": [
            "135013501350",
            "1350",
            "13501350",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "1350"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren bought a phone which costed 7647 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 994 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            82,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "55534",
                "4098"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "55534",
            "4098"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Philippine Tarsier"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "watermelons"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "hairbands"
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bricks or hairbands ?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "bricks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "hairbands"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stout took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5586. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 6 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            931.0,
            0,
            1862.0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 931.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or sugar ?",
        "options": [
            "backpacks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            40,
            20,
            0,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1496,
        "question": "Gaines bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 14 meters, 12 meters, 34 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1496,
            0,
            2992,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Long-Tailed Planigale"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley bought a phone which costed 6914 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 777 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            64,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "Sei whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "grass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 329 olive. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 68 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 120 dollars of its actual cost which is 872 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 25 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            3000,
            0,
            2,
            6000
        ],
        "answer": 3000
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "cookers",
            "pencils",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9922. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 5 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            3968.8,
            30000,
            0,
            1984.4
        ],
        "answer": 1984.4
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "chilli flakes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "visiting cards",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 266?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 261, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            574,
            "can be anything",
            36,
            "261"
        ],
        "answer": 574
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Hebert 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6839 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 19 hens of his village for which he will be paid 3 for each per day. Now he earns 19*3*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "NO",
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 24 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "1512",
            "151215121512",
            1000,
            "15121512"
        ],
        "answer": "1512"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 17 kg of meat in a day. Li 's family consumes 5 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 59?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than pan. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than lader. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1205,
        "question": "Donaldson bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 14 meters, 15 meters, 28 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1205,
            2410,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Elephant seal",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? watermelons or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "polythene covers",
            "watermelons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bumblebee Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jackfruits and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jackfruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Humpback whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "sand",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Kim 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5678 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 17 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 17*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1349,
        "question": "Bright bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 7 meters, 34 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1034.5,
            2698,
            1349
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rich took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9003. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 7 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            1286.142857142857,
            2572.285714285714,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1286.142857142857
    },
    {
        "question": "Hebert bought a phone which costed 5863 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 682 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            56,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "Royal Antelope",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "polythene covers",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Bumblebee Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "Bumblebee Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "cement",
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "disposable glasses",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pumpkins or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkins",
            "ribbons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 144 tomatoes. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 90 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "bobby pins",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 11 kg of meat in a day. Hogan 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            6,
            0,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "5 litre milk cans"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 15 kg of meat in a day. Stout 's family consumes 1 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            30,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Duarte took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6738. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1497.3333333333333,
            748.6666666666666,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 748.6666666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? kettles or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "kettles",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "breadcrumbs"
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Conway in South Carolina for 1 month = 4071. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "4071",
            172
        ],
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of bobby pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bobby pins",
            "jaggery",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Charles 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5465 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 23 hens of his village for which he will be paid 10 for each per day. Now he earns 23*10*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 24 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 500 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 15 tanks?",
        "options": [
            720,
            360,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 104 pomelo. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 46 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of powder . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "powder"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7808. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 3 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            2602.6666666666665,
            5205.333333333333,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2602.6666666666665
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 977?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "candies",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "tree leaves",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 22 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "13861386",
            "1386",
            1000,
            "138613861386"
        ],
        "answer": "1386"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 371 dollars of its actual cost which is 842 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 22 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            16324,
            0,
            8162
        ],
        "answer": 8162
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "lollipops",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Yak",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Curry took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8165. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 12 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            0,
            680.4166666666666,
            1360.8333333333333
        ],
        "answer": 680.4166666666666
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Henry in Georgia for 1 month = 16162. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            303,
            50000,
            "16162"
        ],
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 624?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tomatoes",
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ashley took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 8792. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 10 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            879.2,
            1758.4,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 879.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Conway in New Jersey for 1 month = 13305. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "13305",
            245
        ],
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or paper ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "paper",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "meat",
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce bought a phone which costed 6285 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 577 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            18,
            48,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 195 pear. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 46 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ATM cards",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Paedocypris Fish"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ear plugs",
            "jaggery"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of popsicle sticks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "popsicle sticks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of grass . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "grass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Philippine Tarsier ?",
        "options": [
            " Southern right whale",
            "Philippine Tarsier",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of ear plugs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 14 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "882882882",
            "882882",
            "882",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "882"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Li in Marshall Islands for 1 month = 3336. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "3336",
            50000,
            148
        ],
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "ATM cards",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "4912 students from South Dakota State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1911,
            100,
            5733,
            3822
        ],
        "answer": 1911
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of pencils . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pencils",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or pencils ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pencils",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "pencils"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "small diamonds"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic plates",
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper",
            "butter"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1851,
        "question": "Hebert bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 11 meters, 37 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1851,
            3702,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 31 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 752 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 12 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            744,
            372,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of chilli flakes . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "chilli flakes",
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcgrath bought a phone which costed 9712 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 987 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            7,
            2,
            82,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Blue Whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or tree leaves ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tree leaves",
            "thermos flask"
        ],
        "answer": "tree leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7119. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1582.0,
            791.0,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 791.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 9 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            "567567",
            1000,
            "567567567",
            "567"
        ],
        "answer": "567"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "23502",
                "36130"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "23502",
            "36130"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "iron",
            "tree leaves"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "1756 students from Alabama State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            2331,
            1554,
            777
        ],
        "answer": 777
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "ear plugs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 302 dollars of its actual cost which is 747 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 26 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            15704,
            7852,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 7852
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "7620",
                "52012"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "7620",
            "52012"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "nails",
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cox took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 7976. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1772.4444444444443,
            886.2222222222222,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 886.2222222222222
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Javan rhinoceros",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of sand and 1 kg of safety pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "safety pins",
            "sand"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or lollipops ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "lollipops"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "disposable glasses"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of small diamonds . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Jessie 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9622 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 12 hens of his village for which he will be paid 6 for each per day. Now he earns 12*6*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 389 chicken. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 75 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            15,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            100,
            1000000,
            200
        ],
        "answer": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gaines bought a phone which costed 9538 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 577 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            48,
            0,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 314, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            22,
            925,
            "314"
        ],
        "answer": 925
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Gilbert 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 5638 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 32 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 32*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Somali ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            160,
            1000000,
            80
        ],
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of disposable glasses . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "disposable glasses",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 16 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 8 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "11521152",
            "115211521152",
            "1152"
        ],
        "answer": "1152"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jessie took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5053. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 7 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            721.8571428571429,
            1443.7142857142858,
            30000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 721.8571428571429
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "55507",
                "4125"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "55507",
            "4125"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Pygmy Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Mouse Lemur"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            25,
            50,
            1000000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Moyer in Delaware for 1 month = 17681. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            "17681",
            50000,
            425
        ],
        "answer": 425
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bowhead whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bowhead whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Bowhead whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "39056",
                "20576"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "39056",
            "20576"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ice",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 10 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 884 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 24 tanks?",
        "options": [
            240,
            0,
            2,
            480
        ],
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "disposable plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 56, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "56",
            571,
            31,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 571
    },
    {
        "answer": 1701,
        "question": "Sims bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 6 meters, 39 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            3402,
            1701,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Barbados Threadsnake",
            "Saltwater crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 329 dollars of its actual cost which is 980 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 21 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            6909,
            0,
            13818,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 6909
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bricks",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "15012",
                "44620"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "15012",
            "44620"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of wall pins . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wall pins"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of puffed rice . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "puffed rice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                "3036",
                "56596"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "3036",
            "56596"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Bee Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "African bush elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "33751",
                "25881"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "33751",
            "25881"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian gaur\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6094. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            30000,
            1523.5,
            3047.0
        ],
        "answer": 1523.5
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "drum can fill the pond faster than cooker. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or visiting cards ?",
        "options": [
            "visiting cards",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "visiting cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buckley bought a phone which costed 9950 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 691 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            6,
            56
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 216 dollars of its actual cost which is 898 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 26 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            5616,
            11232,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5616
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 275, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "275",
            16,
            972,
            "can be anything"
        ],
        "answer": 972
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 478?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tom bought a phone which costed 5602 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 646 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            52,
            13,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero",
            "Asian elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or shells ?",
        "options": [
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "shells"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic plates and 1 kg of flowers . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "flowers",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic plates"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian gaur\t or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian gaur\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian gaur\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or bobby pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "shoe boxes",
            "bobby pins"
        ],
        "answer": "bobby pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Long-Tailed Planigale ?",
        "options": [
            "Long-Tailed Planigale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps",
            "books"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                "45844",
                "13788"
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "45844",
            "13788"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 326?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or keys ?",
        "options": [
            "bottles",
            "keys",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ice and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ice"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "dog",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "teak wood",
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 10 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 3 months ?",
        "options": [
            "270270",
            1000,
            "270270270",
            "270"
        ],
        "answer": "270"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of hairbands . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "hairbands",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "Sei whale",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tablets",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Jessie in Northern Mariana Islands for 1 month = 12496. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            940,
            "12496"
        ],
        "answer": 940
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 495?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren bought a phone which costed 6700 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 655 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            54,
            2,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African bush elephant or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider",
            "African bush elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African bush elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 24 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 7 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "15121512",
            "1512",
            "151215121512"
        ],
        "answer": "1512"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 48 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            "4752",
            "475247524752",
            "47524752",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "4752"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Freeman 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9437 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 39 hens of his village for which he will be paid 1 for each per day. Now he earns 39*1*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Crocodile",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 139 salal berry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 72 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Thorius Arboreus"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 298 dollars of its actual cost which is 737 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 48 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            28608,
            2,
            14304,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 14304
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "glass"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bananas"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Southern right whale",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "storage tank can fill the pond faster than mug. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 5558. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 4 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            2779.0,
            1389.5,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1389.5
    },
    {
        "question": "If 50 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 713 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 30 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1500,
            3000
        ],
        "answer": 1500
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour",
            "sugar"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "3614 students from Guam State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            2274,
            4548,
            6822,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2274
    },
    {
        "question": "Moyer has Rs 4993 with him. He wants to buy currant. One kg of currant costs Rs 38. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of currant?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? cookers or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "cookers"
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "Slender Blind Snake",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of glass and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "glass",
            "pepper",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of sugar . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "sugar",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "Vaquita",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "thermocol balls"
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of tree leaves . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "tree leaves",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1413,
        "question": "Crosby bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 16 meters, 14 meters, 31 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2826,
            1034.5,
            1413
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? shoe boxes or breadcrumbs ?",
        "options": [
            "shoe boxes",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "breadcrumbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 152, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            28,
            "152",
            "can be anything",
            880
        ],
        "answer": 880
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or cat ?",
        "options": [
            "cat",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Royal Antelope ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Royal Antelope"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 104 grape. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 38 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            6,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 713?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ceramic cups",
            "shells"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rich bought a phone which costed 5407 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 819 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            13,
            68,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr has Rs 3330 with him. He wants to buy physalis. One kg of physalis costs Rs 19. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of physalis?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1000,
            0,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "salt",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur ?",
        "options": [
            "Madame Berthe’s Mouse Lemur",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Giant Eland\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or candies ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "candies"
        ],
        "answer": "candies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bradford took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6814. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            1514.2222222222222,
            757.1111111111111,
            0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 757.1111111111111
    },
    {
        "answer": 1378,
        "question": "Bridges bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 15 meters, 8 meters, 33 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            1378,
            2756,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 442 dollars of its actual cost which is 641 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 31 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            27404,
            13702
        ],
        "answer": 13702
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 271?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "3609 students from Iowa State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 5 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            1782,
            100,
            891,
            2673
        ],
        "answer": 891
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 260 dollars of its actual cost which is 640 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 35 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            9100,
            18200
        ],
        "answer": 9100
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "feather",
            "big stone"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of pearls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pearls",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Carr bought a phone which costed 8226 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 543 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            44,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "Capybara"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or feather ?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "feather"
    },
    {
        "question": "Duarte bought a phone which costed 7018 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 671 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            2,
            16,
            0,
            54
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "teak wood"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 281 dollars of its actual cost which is 685 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 23 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            6463,
            12926,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 6463
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Bruce in Pennsylvania for 1 month = 10376. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "10376",
            982
        ],
        "answer": 982
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "ear plugs",
            "balloons",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Asian elephant",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of crayons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "potatoes",
            "crayons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Humpback whale or Spruce-fir Moss Spider ?",
        "options": [
            "Humpback whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Spruce-fir Moss Spider"
        ],
        "answer": "Humpback whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 213 dollars of its actual cost which is 722 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 28 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            2,
            11928,
            0,
            5964
        ],
        "answer": 5964
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 324 salal berry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 66 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            12,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce bought a phone which costed 8132 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 690 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            13,
            56,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "Conley bought a phone which costed 6468 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 600 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            50,
            0,
            2,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 133, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            36,
            "can be anything",
            522,
            "133"
        ],
        "answer": 522
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of cotton candy . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "cotton candy"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Chervy 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 6481 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 20 hens of his village for which he will be paid 9 for each per day. Now he earns 20*9*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO",
            "YES"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Gray whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 157 feijoa. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 51 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            3,
            6,
            9,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 466 dollars of its actual cost which is 718 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 44 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            20504,
            2,
            0,
            41008
        ],
        "answer": 20504
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "wall pins",
            "fluffy teddy bears"
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or salt ?",
        "options": [
            "salt",
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of potatoes and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "potatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conway took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 6138. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 11 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            30000,
            1116.0,
            0,
            558.0
        ],
        "answer": 558.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t",
            "Pygmy Marmoset"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of ATM cards . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ATM cards",
            "gold",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "salt",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Javan rhinoceros or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "Javan rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Javan rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "titanium",
            "feather"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or ribbons ?",
        "options": [
            "ribbons",
            "tumblers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "ribbons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko",
            "Fin whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of books and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "books",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "stress balls",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 480?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 703?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? backpacks or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "backpacks",
            "foam"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Capybara",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "socks",
            "meat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of socks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "socks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? jackfruits or ear plugs ?",
        "options": [
            "jackfruits",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ear plugs"
        ],
        "answer": "ear plugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "foam",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "water tanker can fill the pond faster than small tub. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "jaggery",
            "stem barks"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or polythene covers ?",
        "options": [
            "basket balls",
            "polythene covers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "polythene covers"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1000000,
            25,
            50
        ],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Capybara or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "Capybara",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Capybara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Vaquita ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Vaquita",
            "Common ostrich"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1171,
        "question": "Gallegos bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 19 meters, 9 meters, 27 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1034.5,
            2342,
            0,
            1171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of visiting card . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "visiting card"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            4,
            1000000,
            0,
            2
        ],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giant Eland\t or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "Giant Eland\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giant Eland\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian elephant or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Asian elephant",
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? pots or safety pins ?",
        "options": [
            "safety pins",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "pots"
        ],
        "answer": "safety pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? 5 litre milk cans or ATM cards ?",
        "options": [
            "5 litre milk cans",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "ATM cards"
        ],
        "answer": "ATM cards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Atlantic right whale or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "North Atlantic right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Atlantic right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Hippocampus Denise"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 34 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 782 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 20 tanks?",
        "options": [
            680,
            0,
            2,
            1360
        ],
        "answer": 680
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            0,
            40,
            80,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Mary in Hawaii for 1 month = 12746. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            230,
            "12746",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "answer": 1331,
        "question": "Brooks bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 11 meters, 11 meters, 33 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            1331,
            0,
            2662,
            1034.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Indian rhinoceros",
            "Dwarf Three-Toed Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Hippocampus Denise ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippocampus Denise",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? American bison or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "American bison",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "American bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Asian Guar or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "Asian Guar",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Asian Guar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Gray whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Chihuahua",
            "Gray whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Gray whale"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 625?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sperm whale or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sperm whale"
        ],
        "answer": "Sperm whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat",
            "Yak"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "Common ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "dog"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of butter and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "butter",
            "ribbons",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 10 kg of meat in a day. Crosby 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            6,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 gallon storage bladder  can fill the pond faster than hand-palm. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "false"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "tomatoes",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks has Rs 4490 with him. He wants to buy jujube. One kg of jujube costs Rs 19. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of jujube?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian rhinoceros or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "Indian rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 42 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 932 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 14 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            588,
            2,
            1176
        ],
        "answer": 588
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 408, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            18,
            "408",
            526
        ],
        "answer": 526
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Bison",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 254 dollars of its actual cost which is 823 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 54 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            27432,
            13716
        ],
        "answer": 13716
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                0,
                0
            ],
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "509",
                "59123"
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "509",
            "59123"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of stress balls . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stress balls",
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 13 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 11 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "128712871287",
            "1287",
            "12871287"
        ],
        "answer": "1287"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper clips"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "answer": 1325,
        "question": "Day bought 3 square fields A,B,C with sides being 12 meters, 5 meters, 34 meters respectively. What is the total area he owns?",
        "options": [
            2650,
            1034.5,
            0,
            1325
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Bee Hummingbird ?",
        "options": [
            "Bee Hummingbird",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "African forest elephant",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than bottle. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bricks and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bricks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "pepper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Ron in Wisconsin for 1 month = 1995. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            700,
            "1995",
            50000
        ],
        "answer": 700
    },
    {
        "question": "Booker bought a phone which costed 9247 dollars. Life of a phone battery is 980 hours. On using it daily 24/7 , we can guess that the phone battery is still remaining on day: ? (Here range is from the day it is bought upto the day the battery lasts)",
        "options": [
            0,
            80,
            2,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            500,
            1000000,
            250,
            0
        ],
        "answer": "250"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of thermocol . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or dog ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "dog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 45 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 6 months ?",
        "options": [
            "2430",
            "243024302430",
            "24302430",
            1000
        ],
        "answer": "2430"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Yak or Brookesia Micra Chameleon ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Yak",
            "Brookesia Micra Chameleon"
        ],
        "answer": "Yak"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of nails . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "nails"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Giraffe or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? bottles or gift wraps ?",
        "options": [
            "gift wraps",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "bottles"
        ],
        "answer": "gift wraps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? thermos flask or crayons ?",
        "options": [
            "crayons",
            "thermos flask",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "crayons"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "watermelon",
            "kite",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of bananas and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bananas",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Williams’ Dwarf Gecko ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Williams’ Dwarf Gecko"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of rice bag and 1 kg of salt . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "rice bag",
            "salt"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "10000 biscuits can be shared exactly by how many students?",
        "options": [
            8,
            0,
            16,
            1000000
        ],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 34 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 791 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 23 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1564,
            2,
            782
        ],
        "answer": 782
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "African Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 180, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            50,
            922,
            "can be anything",
            "180"
        ],
        "answer": 922
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Valentine in Minnesota for 1 month = 7345. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            "7345",
            340
        ],
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Southern right whale or Pygmy Marmoset ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Pygmy Marmoset",
            " Southern right whale"
        ],
        "answer": " Southern right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "bread"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of watermelon and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "watermelon",
            "lollipops"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 23 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 567 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 18 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            414,
            828,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tomatoes and 1 kg of stem barks . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "stem barks",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tomatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Thorius Arboreus ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak bear\t",
            "Thorius Arboreus",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Warren in Guam for 1 month = 6342. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            937,
            "6342"
        ],
        "answer": 937
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Paedocypris Fish ?",
        "options": [
            "Paedocypris Fish",
            "Elephant seal",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or wall pins ?",
        "options": [
            "wall pins",
            "juicers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "wall pins"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 17 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 658 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 10 tanks?",
        "options": [
            0,
            170,
            340,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or pepper ?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls"
        ],
        "answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Bison or Pygmy Rabbit ?",
        "options": [
            "Bison",
            "Pygmy Rabbit",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Bison"
    },
    {
        "answer": "YES",
        "question": "Hebert 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 8287 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 36 hens of his village for which he will be paid 8 for each per day. Now he earns 36*8*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "titanium"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 16 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 6 months ?",
        "options": [
            "864",
            "864864",
            1000,
            "864864864"
        ],
        "answer": "864"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "lizard",
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "wheat flour"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of feather . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "feather",
            "fruits",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of teak wood and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "lollipops",
            "teak wood",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "ceramic cups",
            "paper clips",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 333 mulberry. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 42 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            21,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "answer": "QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 739?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kitti’s Hog-Nosed Bat"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of tamarind and 1 kg of bread . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bread",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tamarind"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of gold and 1 kg of gift wraps . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "gift wraps",
            "gold"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "Blue Whale",
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of bones . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "bones",
            "cement",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 18 kg of meat in a day. Valentine 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            1,
            12,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or popsicle sticks ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "popsicle sticks",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "popsicle sticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak Bear"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a Fleming in California for 1 month = 18832. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            724,
            "18832"
        ],
        "answer": 724
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Etruscan Shrew"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? fluffy teddy bears or thermocol balls ?",
        "options": [
            "thermocol balls",
            "fluffy teddy bears",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "thermocol balls"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 233, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            800,
            21,
            "233"
        ],
        "answer": 800
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NO",
        "question": "Webster 's father has taken a loan for farming and has to pay 9437 every month to repay the loan. He looks after 38 hens of his village for which he will be paid 6 for each per day. Now he earns 38*6*30 per month. Does he earn enough amount every month that helps him repay the loan?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "Cannot answer",
            "NO"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or lizard ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "lizard"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? balloons or flowers ?",
        "options": [
            "balloons",
            "flowers",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity "
        ],
        "answer": "flowers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? basket balls or tablets ?",
        "options": [
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "basket balls",
            "tablets"
        ],
        "answer": "tablets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salary of a York in Puerto Rico for 1 month = 12124. He can save some amount if he spends how much?",
        "options": [
            50000,
            688,
            "12124"
        ],
        "answer": 688
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedocypris",
            "White rhinoceros\t"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of jaggery and 1 kg of lollipops . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "jaggery",
            "lollipops",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Blue Whale or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Chihuahua",
            "Blue Whale",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "4609 students from Utah State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 3 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            9441,
            3147,
            6294
        ],
        "answer": 3147
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 358?",
        "options": [
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Government is helping farmers buy a cow by paying 277 dollars of its actual cost which is 764 dollars. If the farmers in the state bought around 21 cows. How much did the farmers save on the cows?",
        "options": [
            5817,
            11634,
            2,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 5817
    },
    {
        "question": "1641 students from New York State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            1171,
            3513,
            2342
        ],
        "answer": 1171
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Saltwater crocodile or Etruscan Shrew ?",
        "options": [
            "Etruscan Shrew",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Saltwater crocodile"
        ],
        "answer": "Saltwater crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Cape buffalo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of disposable plates . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "disposable plates",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of wheat flour and 1 kg of paper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "wheat flour",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "paper"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 346 tomato. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 32 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            10,
            20,
            30,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? White rhinoceros\t or Speckled Padloper Tortoise ?",
        "options": [
            "Speckled Padloper Tortoise",
            "White rhinoceros\t",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "White rhinoceros\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of tablets . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "tablets",
            "iron"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of fruits and 1 kg of balloons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "fruits",
            "balloons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Fin whale or Monte Iberia Eleuth ?",
        "options": [
            "Fin whale",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Monte Iberia Eleuth"
        ],
        "answer": "Fin whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Valentine has Rs 4096 with him. He wants to buy plum. One kg of plum costs Rs 21. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of plum?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Hippopotamus or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 652?",
        "options": [
            "QUALIFIED",
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd took a debt from his relative to buy a phone for Rs 9045. He is expected to pay it back in equal amounts every month for 9 months. How much amount does he have to pay per month?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1005.0,
            2010.0,
            30000
        ],
        "answer": 1005.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak Bear or Chihuahua ?",
        "options": [
            "Kodiak Bear",
            "Chihuahua",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak Bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of cement and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "cement"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Alaskan Moose\t or Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa ?",
        "options": [
            "Alaskan Moose\t",
            "Baluchistan Pygmy Jerboa",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Alaskan Moose\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Kodiak bear\t or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Kodiak bear\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Kodiak bear\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? juicers or foam ?",
        "options": [
            "foam",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "juicers"
        ],
        "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
        "question": "1224 students from Indiana State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 8 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            100,
            2973,
            1982,
            991
        ],
        "answer": 991
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of titanium and 1 kg of ribbons . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "titanium",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "ribbons"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A foodcourt owner has 460 pineapple. He puts them in delivery boxes. Each box can accomodate 66 food items. How many delivery boxes does he need?",
        "options": [
            6,
            12,
            18,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Cape buffalo or Dwarf Lantern Shark ?",
        "options": [
            "Cape buffalo",
            "Dwarf Lantern Shark",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Cape buffalo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Somali ostrich or Brookesia Micra ?",
        "options": [
            "Somali ostrich",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Brookesia Micra"
        ],
        "answer": "Somali ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "2727 students from Alaska State went on a camping trip. Each tent can accomodate a group of 7 students. Students can accomodate more comfortably if the number of tents is ?",
        "options": [
            4470,
            100,
            2980,
            1490
        ],
        "answer": 1490
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Crocodile or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Crocodile",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog"
        ],
        "answer": "Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier?  Black rhinoceros or Barbados Threadsnake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            " Black rhinoceros",
            "Barbados Threadsnake"
        ],
        "answer": " Black rhinoceros"
    },
    {
        "question": "rain can fill the pond faster than scooper. true or false ",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "both can fill the pond faster",
            "none of them can fill the pond faster",
            "true"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "answer": "NOT QUALIFIED",
        "question": "Cut-off for a competitive exam is 70% of its total marks. Total marks being 1000, can the student get qualified if his score is 437?",
        "options": [
            "NOT QUALIFIED",
            "CANNOT BE DETERMINED",
            "QUALIFIED"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? North Pacific right whale or Slender Blind Snake ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "North Pacific right whale",
            "Slender Blind Snake"
        ],
        "answer": "North Pacific right whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "33080",
                "26552"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "33080",
            "26552"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If 27 buckets can be filled with one tank full of water with 900 liters. How many buckets can we fill with water of 17 tanks?",
        "options": [
            2,
            918,
            0,
            459
        ],
        "answer": 459
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of ceramic cups and 1 kg of paper clips . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "paper clips",
            "ceramic cups",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Indian Elephant\t or rat ?",
        "options": [
            "rat",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Indian Elephant\t"
        ],
        "answer": "Indian Elephant\t"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of big stone and 1 kg of pepper . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pepper",
            "big stone",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hess has Rs 4078 with him. He wants to buy physalis. One kg of physalis costs Rs 49. His money is sufficient to buy how many kgs of physalis?(range is from 1 kg to maximum he can buy with his amount)",
        "options": [
            1,
            1000,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of meat and 1 kg of breadcrumbs . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "breadcrumbs",
            "meat"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Price of one litre of milk = Rs 9. We know that the cow gives 21 litre of milk in one month. Considering farmer sells the entire milk every month, how much does he earn in 4 months ?",
        "options": [
            1000,
            "756756",
            "756756756",
            "756"
        ],
        "answer": "756"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Elephant seal or Leptotyphlops carlae ?",
        "options": [
            "Elephant seal",
            "Leptotyphlops carlae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant seal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Sei whale or Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Sei whale",
            "Virgin Island Dwarf Sphaero"
        ],
        "answer": "Sei whale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given a container of 10 kg volume, which object can be filled in more quantity? tumblers or small diamonds ?",
        "options": [
            "small diamonds",
            "both the objects can be filled in equal quantity ",
            "tumblers"
        ],
        "answer": "small diamonds"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of iron and 1 kg of shells . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "iron",
            "shells",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    },
    {
        "question": "A tiger consumes 19 kg of meat in a day. Blanchard 's family consumes 3 kg meat a day. If the amount of meat consumed by tiger per day is given to the family, they still have the meat on day number:  ?",
        "options": [
            2,
            12,
            0
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Addition of two numbers x and y is 59632. What can be the values of x and y ?",
        "options": [
            [
                59632,
                59632
            ],
            [
                "32157",
                "27475"
            ],
            [
                0,
                0
            ]
        ],
        "answer": [
            "32157",
            "27475"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? Common ostrich or Paedocypris ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Common ostrich",
            "Paedocypris"
        ],
        "answer": "Common ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African forest elephant or Paedophryne Amauensis Frog ?",
        "options": [
            "both are of equal weight",
            "Paedophryne Amauensis Frog",
            "African forest elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "African forest elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is heavier? African Elephant or Sphaerodactylus Ariasae ?",
        "options": [
            "African Elephant",
            "Sphaerodactylus Ariasae",
            "both are of equal weight"
        ],
        "answer": "African Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cost price of a toy is 239, the owner is considered to be on profit if the selling price is ?",
        "options": [
            "can be anything",
            971,
            26,
            "239"
        ],
        "answer": 971
    },
    {
        "question": "You are given 1 kg of pumpkin and 1 kg of kite . Which is heavier?",
        "options": [
            "pumpkin",
            "both are of equal weight",
            "kite"
        ],
        "answer": "both are of equal weight"
    }
]